This almost feels illegal to know if you're a side sleeper.
What I've discovered could save you from a massive mistake that's crushing your body
while you sleep.
Crazy visions of me as a special place where boys and girls can all be queens every single
day.
I'm the wicked dreams of leaving Tennessee.
You Santa Monica, I swear it's calling me.
It's gonna cause a scene. She sees her baby girl. I know she's gonna scream
Got memes out here from Tennessee. Oh Santa Monica. You've been too good to me.
Make my mama. It's gonna cause a scene. She sees her baby girl. I know she's gonna scream
Always on my mind. Yeah, you're seven miles away.
Isn't it? It's okay. Do you know Chapel Roan? She's like a I don't know. Maybe yeah, I've never seen her before
That's a nice song. How are you doing tonight? Oh, I'm so pissed man
I don't want to be dragged into this bullshit the other day
He was threatening me and and you know because I went off on him
I was done and he was going on about gamble and I eat that kill myself and fuck you and all this crazy shit
Oh my god, you know and and and he's acting that way again. I see that guy in that video that they shared
That's like a psychopath and I'm done. I told him I'd give him one more chance
He's being psycho and the dox or they're saying you the dox or he's the one doxing people
You know, and I'll show everything he has my my text now number, but that's how communicate, but I'm done with him
He's starting more shit by going in her her chat. Why is he fucking with her?
Well, I know I mean how dare he go in there and ask for two thousand, you know, send
Now it's gonna go into her like I'm extorting or trying to extort or something. Yeah, and we're being blamed too
I didn't know anything about that
No, I don't know anything. I'm not I don't ask me for anything. Well, John, you can think about everyone. I mean, it's like, you know, that's why I basically leave my channel for anyone when they want. And I don't know. I don't see. Hi, Rose red. Well, I so I don't know what's going on. I mean, it's like basically, like, I think he has like, uh, like an anger, anger issue or something like that. But I mean, if he was ever to come on again.
I really will ask him or out of control out of control anger, you know, and he and I told him stop that
You know and he keeps on and then she's mentioning us again saying we're extorting when he's the one in her chats
It's like leave people leave her alone. Why are you chatting about money?
That is extortion and that's him doing it right and I don't want to be associated with like, you know
It's crazy the crazies are all enemies now could he has seen this like coming a mile away
Who are you John like it? Yeah, who are you John Stockton? You're nobody. That's probably him. Yeah, it's probably him
Yeah, yeah, and then and then all your chat everybody saw that everybody dropped off because of him there and then he went
Up on bad boy breeze. What did bad boy breeze do bad boy breeze was a new new person in the chat that I was enjoying like you know
It's interesting right yeah, he's a nice guy
I thought he was more of like a public
Big I mean I just subscribe to this channel. He has a nice channel. There's some people. I've done
Slightly, but yeah, I mean I told him to come back to my chat and I I promised like you know, I
Just I don't I don't see I don't know all the backstory or all the
The stuff about it, so I can't really say oh is this person out of the closet and well
No, I'm not a closet or is this person here on a quiet level and so that that's very disrespectful brand
I mean, I don't I don't know what I mean
I just don't want to be associated with what he says
I mean, it's yeah me either with that and his behavior and then going in the chat and and demanding
One K and two K
I told him I'd give him one more chance, but this is too much, you know
I mean, this is ridiculous and to go on and on and on about gamble. Come on. Just leave it alone and do your thing
Yeah, I mean I've learned from the stuff that I've done years ago and that stopped and I never got in trouble in 82
I was in college
So yeah, it's a she asked me to help support him and everything and I tried and then look at him
He just goes nuts on everybody. I have this image. I next check out the screen. Hold on a second
Here we go. Okay, so we have the INX files. So so this is yeah from a long time ago
Yeah, and so like what is and so hold on so the she's saying she's calling in psyche
Yeah, we're she's calling us the toxic personalities
And then it says, you know, it says,
both attain personal information for love.
These are all just accusations, by the way.
And then this is the obsessions.
It really touched you to beat his panel initials
and a cat on his body.
Well, the cat is my cat, right?
But look, I mean, this is so crazy.
The weaponization of the private DMs,
which he's taking your private DMs, weaponizing them.
Advice, keep talking to public panels, okay?
The cease and desist of, it says our cease and desist letters.
Yes, it's good. It's buying attorney because he said yeah email it to her and I did and she's
I mean we there she's an assist on these on these on these specific claims
He's saying too. He's watching I sent him everything so yeah, yeah, and so that's that I mean I have that
I mean I also have another analysis of like, you know this
What is this one right here? I mean, yeah, she looks a little bit she's not she doesn't have dwarfism
I promise you guys, but yeah, this is like see we had
See this was us, you know months and I say I went through this thing about the swan and rumpel stills can ever this one
Can't the swank, you know the ugly duckling turns into the swan
And I read rumpel still skin where she like knows rumpel still skin name on that episode Alice came on and said
The relationship is revolves around knowing and naming each other and Alexander claiming to see the true psyche
Which was my name beneath a persona and so she said oh you're not psyching anymore
You're just John because you look like a John because I I was a professional sex worker
That's what she said and that you know that so I so she knows John's and look at there's there's like RG
There like in that little frowny face
Bond is solidified through mutual hatred of external figures like go. I love ghosts. What is this RG mocked and I like ghosts too
Yeah, I like those. Have you talked to him today?
No, he he did text me and it was really late last night or early this morning
So I need to mod my friend. Hey oceans if you're around can you come up because I really we really need a good spiritual
Person, I don't know if you can you have some sage or something if you can talk to my friend care
We've been we need some we need some sage
is a really wise person.
She also, she just made this,
see all those emojis she made?
Those all have a specific message to them.
It's like a code you can figure out.
I mean, I just, I didn't hear her as a moderator,
but it says, see, let me look at it says,
wave, smiley face.
And she has cowboy.
Cowboys are cat.
Then she has to see the cowboy cat.
And then she has-
Oh, that's cool.
Yeah. And then she has a heart.
And then she has an alien UFO.
Cause she's maybe, yeah, she's meant to be a duck.
Oh, she's gonna come up.
Okay.
You're going to put the link.
Oh, cool.
You'll love her.
Something positive.
Yeah, I want to see that.
I want to sub through her.
She has that stuff.
Oh, she has a channel.
She does reading stuff.
She does great readings.
She, she, oh, really?
Yeah.
She has a cat named Cowboy.
He's really cute.
And, oh, wow.
You'll love her.
I mean, you'll love her.
I mean, you'll mean her in a second.
She's real, real smart.
She also does these gummy mushrooms.
I don't know.
She does.
I heard about those.
the real mushrooms or mushrooms?
I've always had to figure that out.
I'm like, are these good mushrooms
or are they some kind of health mushroom?
But yeah, I've seen the health mushroom.
Because, yeah, I've modded you.
Make sure to drop your channel with you.
So she has a channel called, well, her name is the Diana,
right?
And then she has a channel called dot d.
And we call her Oceans.
Uh, and she has a channel. Oh, here she is. Let's let's say hi to her. Oh, cool. Okay. Hi
Welcome to the show. Can I see me?
Hi me this is Aya next you're talking to my next and
I keep missing you. What's up?
Oh, I'm not Maja. I'm on a backup channel right now, but
I'm
Hey, where's your way?
Oh, you got your
Hey, I don't have my fun here on ocean. Tell the story of like ocean was a street performer at one time
Well, I could go back. I could just go back and make that avatar, but you know, do it
Well, you were a stripper what instrument did you play on the street?
Remember you played an instrument and then some guy tried to poop in your guitar case or something and you you
Almost I played guitar and also took my hands
Oh my God, yeah, he goes, I have nothing to give you and so I will give you what I turned and turned around and pull down his drawers and tried to loop in my guitar.
Oh my God.
And what did you do with your cane?
Make you taste the end of it the hard way, my friend.
Yeah, that's a fun list.
But also, you've had a near-death experience too.
But Karen was, or INX was asking about if you do reading.
I mean, I know sometimes you do reading,
sometimes you do more of like the channeling.
You do tarot, you're also very spiritual in general.
You astral project like crazy, right?
I thought it was in my phone.
All right, okay, well, hopefully she's back.
Well, hopefully I didn't scare her away.
I know I'm here watching and I'm like,
guess what, I'm drinking some voodoo rangers tonight.
I've already had a voodoo ranger.
I'm almost done with this one,
but I'm having a couple of voodoo rangers tonight.
We've got the pet store today.
And,
Hey, you're oh, you want to see Lola and oceans oceans. Yeah, you want to see Lola, you know the name cowboy
Maybe that's what I should I should name a boy cat cowboy. That's a good name. It is my dad
I know right. I didn't know what to name him. It's like, yeah
That wasn't even my dad's dog. He had a dog that he loved it was his last
little dog that he just called his own dog. Hey Nancy, how are you? You know
reality Nancy like really nice and nice person but she went on and she was
being attacked about Brandon tonight on another show. Really him too? Yeah, I don't
understand why his anger gets me help. I mean backstage I mean would you like to
can we have a discussion? Oh she's back.
Brandon's backstage. Oh, no, I'm not gonna talk to him because uh, you know, this is ridiculous. I'm done
Okay, he went too far and now she keeps going on about us all when he should should have stayed out of her chat
Yeah
Please don't please don't make the man's name to Alex. No, I don't want to talk to him. That's why I'm straight it out
I'm done with him. I'm not gonna give him another chance. You know, I'm done. It's a psyche. So don't bring him up
Okay, we're gonna have to type in the back chat. He's typing the private. Yeah
This is too far because if I have to because I do have an attorney on it
I'm just gonna give him every every
Ridiculous, I'm not gonna be used for this bullshit though. You know, I've already done a lot of shit in the past
when I was heavily on drugs, you know,
and I'm not gonna do this shit again.
I'm not there to be used to go at people.
What happened, she's asking, so is there a specific?
What she did, she's making post-docs in us too
and blaming us and saying that we're all
extorting money from her and somebody looked at it,
my attorney, and he said, that is pretty bad
and cut it off, though, that's dangerous.
That's a dangerous person.
Okay, cuz I don't need this shit, you know now, you know, you don't do that the man people give money and he's that's the second time and
She's blaming us. I didn't even know that happened until somebody sent it to me
You know, I I did I did the
season desist by email like the attorney said and here she's mentioning us because of him still fucking with her
It's just weird. We're not in her chats. Yeah
I know I have
And so I haven't been back on ulcer or anything
Alexandra and her chat he's writing backstage like crazy. I mean, what does he say he's saying I didn't do anything
Yes, he did. She posted it. It shows him in the chat
He's gonna donate $30 to the cats if I let him up. Can we like well? No, I'll give you $40 to keep him off
Okay, I'll give it more. So yeah
Keep him off and I'm recording this I'm done
Maybe he needs to make an apology to her because she was helping him and just because she was talking
to an enemy he just flipped out first he said he uh it was okay then two days later all of a sudden
she's talking to this person that person that person and I thought you know what yeah he's
right but he went too far well look at Lola's face look at Lola's face oh wow she looks just like
I think he's trying to start a bidding war.
I just don't want him to go to escalate and stuff like that.
I mean, it's like, so whoever it is.
Oh, I'll give you more, I'll give you more, I'm sure.
Okay, well, whoever sends first.
No, I'm going to record him and I'm going to post this
and I'm going to go ahead and file something on him
and show him the text because when the attorney saw that.
He said to a police report.
So no, I'm not supposed to have any communication with him
because I'm going to go ahead and put his name in it.
He sure he needs to apologize towards what he needs to do.
OK.
That's all he needs to do. It's now it's between him and her and he needs to take responsibility because I had no idea
That he was over there demanding money that is extortion
Well, I mean it's a I mean it's a hopefully it's not in my name
I don't know if he was saying oh to send it to psyche and stuff like that
She put our names in it because she said we're involved with that and you know, I don't need that shit
And I don't want to keep on about him. I feel
To work it out. I mean somehow but I mean no not that nothing with me
With your final her with your final thing. Yeah, I mean it's like so yeah, man is yet so um, so everyone's saying I'm choking Lola like
I'll show you Kitty, you know, I'm sad that she just got old and she was just getting like, I don't know, she like awesome didn't know what she was and in my place and she just, I don't know it just she was just getting old and that's what the vet said it's like wow and then said well she is 20.
Okay
$100 now, I'd rather just I mean I read what I'll give you more I'll give you no
He needs to get off of here because I am
And I am gonna go to gamble and I'll join gamble and talk to him about him
So he needs to leave you alone. He's not gonna join any panel with me
Okay, you know
He needs to apologize to her. Here's a good. That's all I ask and we're not gonna talk about him anymore
I want to hear what
Yeah, it's gonna be legal now it's gonna be legal now and I'm gonna go ahead and talk to gamble about it
And you know and see what?
Attorney has to say about it. So he needs to leave me alone and stop trying to join panels because he did that before after he threatened me in
Texas and I have that they're saying go kill yourself all this shit and I gave him one more chance
He said oh, I'm sorry. I flipped out, but this is him every day
And I don't like that person. I don't like that
You have the incense or sage oceans. We it's an emergency
Sage she carries sage
She actually carries sage. She's a she's a she I think she's in Ohio. I mean, I'm not the dog
Not to say too. I think she's in Ohio or not Canada, but she's really cool and
Oceans you hear up seems like it. You can't hear those readings
Oceans
Is your brother in her?
Yeah, I love Lola. Yeah, you love little yeah, I saw these little kids at um
at a PetSmart today, they had these little kits
of full of cat toys, they had these big boxes
they made of all the cat toys.
And that's like the part of the donation
I will take, I'll buy the big box
of the big mystery box of cat toys
and I'll share it and stuff like that because.
Oh, how cute.
I bought a bunch of toys today.
I ordered like $200 worth of stuff for my cats.
I do that every month.
Yeah, toys and I already got the two trees and a tunnel and one room is off the ground
I'm in the two bedroom
Yes, well, they can spoil the kiddies and like, you know, I mean, that's why oh, they are they're so spoiled
Look at this cat's face. Oh, look at this because you know, she'll like kitty. I think a kitty when I see her
I can't seem to say I'm clearing with some cell. Okay. She's gonna clear with some cell and I backstage
So I'll tell you the story of Lola. So when I
Know I got Lola. I have a friend and he's like a little bit of a street urchin kind of person
I mean, you know gang member kind of stuff that he brought me. He's this blonde guy
Whatever he brought over this little he had a cat little little cat here
And I had, I think I had five cats at the time and I was like, there's, I was like, please, I was like, please don't, don't show her to me.
I don't, I can't see her because if I see her, I'll fall in love and then I'll have to keep her.
And then he said, well, look, can I just leave her here for like 10 minutes?
He said, I'll be back in 10 minutes.
So I go, okay, like by 10 minutes later, he's still not come back and then the little carrier is on my couch next to me.
And so I was like, okay, and I opened it up.
And she came out and she had all these bookers in her eyes.
Like her eyes.
It was off the street.
He just got her off the street.
Picture her up off the street.
Oh, and she's so sweet.
She's like the sweetest, like she's very, very loving cat.
She's like, she's the one that if I put my blanket up,
she darts under it.
I can even, I think I might have a short of it someone.
But yeah, oh yeah, we, okay,
Oceans is gonna try to come back up one second.
Comes Oceans.
The sage, ask her about the sage.
Yeah, the sage and the selenite.
Okay, let's see.
Oh, she's, she looks like a little mermaid, doesn't she?
Oh, she looks like, oh my gosh.
I don't know why it's not working.
I mean, she's a streamer, by the way.
I'm gonna post her link in the chat for you guys.
Her name is D-Oceans, woo, okay.
D-Oceans, deep woo, I think it is.
And she is a very talented woman in all kinds of ways.
You know, she's a very good terror reader,
a very good channel.
She's familiar with aliens.
Um, she's familiar with
Astral beings astral
She's familiar with spiritual warfare. She's familiar with politics and in all kinds of cool stuff. So here's her link right there
Okay, oh here she is again, here we go, there's her link right there. Can we hear you now, let's see if I can
Yeah, we hear you now
Yeah, so so I was asking about like, you know, are you doing readings now?
The only thing is is I'm getting an echo and I can't figure out why I
Mean it's like
Two browsers because you sound fine you sound fine and you sound you know you can if there's two browsers open or if there's something
Oh, look at it's on it. So now Brandon is calling me a PDF. Okay. So now Brandon says you're turning
Brandon, you need to chill out. We're not even talking about you. You want it to be about you
were sitting with the spiritual advisor. Now you're saying you're calling me a
I can do something
Yeah, we need help right now. We need sage all of us everybody. I'm a sage
Very wise I am a sage
So damn hot psyche, I didn't feel like putting on any hair. My hair is glued to my heads
like
Well, just do it, psyche. Come on, baby.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
Sorry, I'm so sorry.
Woo-hoo-hoo.
I'm sorry. Okay. I'm sorry. We're a little wilder. I had a beer. Oh, you had a beer?
Yeah, I had a beer. I'd have another one.
Yeah, we just. Yeah, no, right. Like last minute or so. I know, right. It's crazy. Yeah. So you do the sage. What does the sage do? Well, actually, sage just means wise person. But sage is also the herb and the herb that Native Americans use. Yeah, I heard that you're clearing. Yes. What does that do, though?
Well, that is supposed to clear of negative stuff, but there's also other ways to do that too.
I can also use selenite, and I can also just be such a bright, little, shiny, upbeat sucker
that everything gets scared away.
Oh, wow. So that's what it is. It's supposed to scare away, um, like
Yeah, well, it's supposed to dissipate it. Yeah, it's like, it's a clearing.
Yeah, I was wondering what that is. I know they talked about that in movies about devils or, uh,
when they do the exorcism.
Well, there's incense that there's all kinds of incense that people use for their kind of thing. And there's the idea that smoke carries up prayer and carries up intentions.
And changes the vibration of the atmosphere and it does actually change the vibration of the atmosphere and everything is about frequency and vibration. Therefore, anything you do that changes that is going to change your situation.
And in some cases, but I would recommend that you get a hold of some selenite
and in whatever form you can
And you just and you just go ahead and what to sprinkle it around everywhere
Now selenite is a stone. Okay. Oh, what do you do with the stone?
and all you have to do is keep it around you, okay?
Oh, okay.
Kind of wave it around or wear it
and actually you can get necklaces now.
They're not too hard to find.
I'm thinking of just getting a bunch
of what you're selling them to my friend.
Yeah, how do you sell the knife in?
Selenite and Turmaline, because Turmaline is a black stone, it draws in the negatives,
negativity, I can't talk, negativity to itself, the selenite cleanses, will cleanse all your
other stones and your atmosphere, and actually the selenite has been used to purify things
You know for purifying
Spiritually it's also used industrially
But it reflects a lot of light and if you see a piece of especially the fibrous kind of selenite
They're very shiny like when the camera hits it it close. Okay throws a lot of light around now the dark things do not like
Bright light. Okay. It's a bright light bright light. Um
Now and i'm gonna record the calls. Okay, go ahead and stop calling me brandon, okay?
I mean brandon naughty
Naughty brandon
I'm gonna go ahead and block his ass
So I don't want any communications, but
Well, he didn't make me a monster. I can't even do it
I'm so mad now
Uh-oh anybody there or an apology? Oh, I'm sorry. I'm here. Can you hear me?
Here's a crystal I found
Okay, that's a crystal. Yeah, that's a big
My that's an awful big crystal you got there boy
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh wow.
It looks like you have a virus behind you there.
Show the real proof like I do.
Yeah.
No, I'm not involved in any crimes.
Yeah, you don't threaten people.
I would be under the death penalty right now with the crimes I've been accused of just
this past week.
But you know what?
I sit in my house, I pet my cats, I talk online.
That's all I do.
I want to pull a card for you.
Can I pull a card for you, Woo?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to have a card.
I have these cards.
Yeah.
Read for the baby.
Come on.
So let me pull three cards for INX too and then if anyone else wants to you know if you want to
Read for the baby.
Come on.
oh okay so what would we have here oh you love this is this Bridget Bargeau or something like
that this is the Nine of Cubs.
Yeah, I remember that was my mom's favorite. I think was she an actress. I know
Younger somebody actually
Is that the tie in her hand almost like she has the power of the man she has like the brain
She has the happiness if she has almost everything you want almost there's something more
How old is she now? How old is she now? She's still alive.
If you don't mind sharing, Dee, you can give the generational you're in. You might be,
no, I think she's a little bit shy. Dee, do you ocean?
Hello, she's out. What do you want from me?
He's asking about what generation are you going on right now?
Oh
Not her
She's quite old now. Hey, look at this
To be a boomer. You get there. There's you don't want you get the cat there too. Remember your cat samu's cat. Oh, wow the cat
But you got the cat, the firepower, right?
Also, you got the garden.
They're also very powerful.
It's like, don't eff with you.
It's like, you know, well, yeah, you really don't want to mess with me.
And then, well, who's this guy?
There's a king of swords, but he's in reverse.
It's kind of negative for he said negative things or something like that.
But it's like, or this man you've been dealing with.
a negative person kind of trying to hurt your feeling or something like that.
Almost like I almost feel like under attack of trolls or something like that.
It's trying to hurt your feelings. And then it's like...
But I hope you're not trapped in your mind about this because we have the ate a source
Which is usually something about getting second in your mind
It could be about anything, you know, and sometimes it's gonna be in your mind and a little bit guarded
But just know like if you need to step out of it you can
Because you are the emperors you're actually all the queens in the deck. You're all you're all this great stuff
You know, you're hard. I'm every queen in the deck
you're all the queens. You are all the queens. I like this. That's like the eye of the
so you just know everything so you're comfortable. I think they are after. Hey Bridget Barton passed away
in her sleep peacefully in December 28th 2025 at the age of 91 years old. Yeah I remember she was
old and my mom used to like her.
Yeah, she was considered there to be a very sexy female
And Karen's a criminal Karen and Brandon's gonna show all your shit Karen offered money Brandon's evidence on Karen
I don't I'm not a criminal. I don't have a criminal. I had a
Probation in 86 that was the only time and the one that I had was a communication harassment like
And that was, um, that was dismissed or whatever.
They called it deferred.
What did you say?
Something.
Yeah.
So I'm not a criminal.
I never made a jail.
Sure.
I next is a gangster.
You know, but not a criminal.
You know.
Yeah.
I did things and I shouldn't have.
And I did it for a streamer that had us do a lot of shit and I'm done with that.
And that's why I say everybody calm down.
Don't do the shit that we've done.
Just let it go, I mean, if you got to say something, say it on your...
your channel you don't have to go you don't have to turn it into the Jerry
Springer show for guys. Right? Brandon is saying she's insane tell her so now. He's
insane he's insane okay you want me to show I'm gonna go ahead and show the
tags and nasty ones. He's a dumb old cunt. Let me on fuck you if you don't want me out. No fuck you. I don't want anything to do with you. You know what? Let's get gamble on. Let's get gamble on.
He's a lot of gamble do you want to come up to gamble? He said let me say my piece Karen
I'm showing all your text asking. Oh, I'm good. I'll show everything on him to then I'll show everything watch
Watch he's a piece of shit and he needs to leave people alone instead of stalking them
I I was supporting him. I believed him and then I see this horrible side of him
I'm sorry too because I I endorsed him and I was like, you know, I think me too
Yeah, and then and then now I don't see this word pieces of shit because you know, we had it
I mean, it's a big mess. Well, because why is he so insane? I don't get it
You want me to post and share the video of what Gamble showed because it's a full-length video. It's really bad because
Oh, yeah, that's the Brandon did that we were that's talking now just evil and just going nuts
And I've taught that and and all he has to do is go apologize to Alex for trying to tell her to send people money
That's all he has to do. I don't have a membership responsibility
If you want a membership to the show, it's cult codex.me
It's uh the lowest member. Oh, I'll do that. I'll buy membership. Thank you. And you'll get flaccid. Yeah, I don't I don't know
He's he's bucket, you know
He's gonna fuck up if he comes up with me because I don't want shit to do with him
Apologize robot. I was supposed to look at the mods before I started the show. So let me look at the mod. Who's the mod?
It is
Rose red
Rose
That's Brandon. If you have Brandon on, he's probably a blocky or doing something. Who knows?
Trigger, we're not even talking about him and he keeps going on. I mean, he's got to get help get help Brandon
We're talking about something more important. You just need to apologize
Apologize to Alex. Yeah, there's a way to really piss off people like that. Yeah, right
Right, right.
Yeah, and this is harassment.
He doesn't leave people alone.
Can you do a read on this?
You want me to do, I'll go ahead and,
I didn't even watch that whole video yet,
but it was pretty bad from what they were playing.
So the only thing he has to do is apologize to Alex and take responsibility for him saying that demanding
2001,000 who the hell does he think he is? I know
Guys this shows up. That's what it's about. Okay, right. I'm trying to like just live my life
We're trying to do the listen to
to oceans you guys are discussing something more important and all he wants to do is make it about
drama you know we don't have going to oceans is awesome oh so oceans yeah so let's listen to you are
so sweet you know people who harass you should just be slept upside the head until they get some
because we don't need that problem with that bullshit.
I've had enough.
To just ignore the fuck out of him, I'm sorry.
Yeah, ignore him, Psyche, then ignore him.
I have to, I have something to do backstage,
but if you can talk to each other for a minute,
that'd be awesome.
No, I don't want to talk with him, OK?
I've got a charge against him with the tigs.
Accu, oceans to oceans.
Oh, no
I'm recording it. I'm recording
He doesn't know or he's coming in to just start shit psyche. Okay, whatever
Yeah, do you want to talk to him, Ocean?
No, no, no, no, I meant Ocean's talk to you.
Not any of you talk to Brandon. Brandon's saying back.
Oh, okay, okay. Just please don't bring him up.
Because that just starts.
Yeah, don't bring him up.
Because that's what he's waiting for.
Yeah, he runs the drama.
Whatever you all are doing.
What are you doing with your life, dude?
I mean, if all the song and dance you got
is to come on somebody else's show
that is really working his ass off in a way
and nobody realizes what it's like to try and be
doing these shows.
They think we're just flipping a few buttons
and it's easy.
Right, wake it about him.
That's bullshit, dude.
If that's all you've got to do with your life, what?
kind of loser does that show you to be come on the rest of us are seeing mr.
loser you know i mean the whole thing is i don't even know you but i'm sitting here going
oh yeah he's he doesn't even know you but that's his excuse
people what uh why not just start a show your own
Have a nice life
Talking about him. It's like you get get out leave us alone. I mean shit. This is what he does
Go make your own
Make your own friends go to 90 other channels that must be on right now
What you know, what life do you have that this is your whole song and dance?
And this is all you got to do with your life. I felt sorry for you
It's terrible
You poor guy! I mean, jeez, go go find somewhere that actually makes you happy, will ya?
I mean, that's what I'd like to see. Find yourself somewhere that makes you happy, okay?
I- I don't hate you!
I don't I don't even know you
But I know that what we just want you to stop Brandon. She's talking about something more important
Okay, leave it alone. Go to your own channel. I will show everything if you don't leave me alone, okay?
Just leave people alone
The drama
Just time and now
Just timing out. If he won't shut up, he don't have any damn sense.
Yeah, it's always about the drama. I mean, it doesn't have anything going on.
He wants to make it about him.
I do not put up with that shit on my show ever.
Yeah, nobody does.
I do not put up with it.
They get timed out. They get their asses timed out right now.
Or banned.
Oh, I love this song, Psyche.
Thank you.
My new song.
Here I am.
Psyche.
Psyche, I'm working on that.
I'm working on both the music and videos.
I'm really scared you'll most love me up.
Well, how do you do that?
I will help you with it.
Well, you can say you will.
But you better come on with a big name.
I will.
Oh, are you scaring me, Will?
I'm gonna do better.
I love this one.
Oh, it's, uh, I like it.
He's gonna go to jail then.
kings don't waste their energy performing a stay they survive
i'll call you spain
action of clue arms clear stays the impossible to own
where you seek a throne box your path
only one find your future was never outside inside
hey i like that are you gonna post that video
Yeah, I love it. I want to yeah
Did you read what I put in chat in
The ocean's on cycle. I'm doing screenshots of everything. Yeah
This is all big the guys the US government is watching right now. All right. He's paranoid
He's he's crazy
Yeah, I mean he's gonna go to jail, man
Rested before I think Donald Trump is actually in the chat tonight
It's probably gonna see that sad that he's gonna make all these
Fake bots to fuck with people. I mean, let's just ignore him. He's
I want to flex for some for some beautiful women
For oceans
No, but oceans
I'm sorry. Oh Ricky dollar mills are right to tuck anywhere
If I had a dollar bill, I was
Right now. I'll put it my g-string right now
It wouldn't be the red white blue and brown dollar bills are in the wash
Yeah, well
That was dirty money, you know, yeah, I knew it was money laundering, you know
all the time.
You know what's funny is, okay, so I have, I have American flag
Speedo, and I would traditionally on my show, I wear the
Speedo a couple of weeks before the 4th of July. And so the
other, like last week, I was wearing the Speedo on a show.
And somebody, his name is bronze bitch or bronze birders or
bronze chicken, he said, he said, it's not even 4th of July,
why are you wearing the Speedo?
Well, you know what somebody was celebrating the 4th of july on Saturday night. They were blowing
The other
American
All year round. I can wear American flag speedo any day. I want and that's my right. So can you carry the oceans?
I did when I was in the same team I was like in elementary school and I didn't like doing this
I wore these red speedos
When I was a kid I had to do junior lifeguards and I had to be in red
And my family would point at me and say,
oh, look, we can see your wiener.
It's a studio.
It was a studio.
They were popular back then.
Yeah, so what is wrong with that?
But you know what?
I swam in 40 seconds bath for anybody else.
So like, you say, like, it's a bad thing.
What's your problem?
I would just get naked and swim in the pool.
I was a fast swimmer.
Was it fast? Oh, you were yeah, I was I bet you wouldn't be without yeah
I was just like there's the blood in the pool was terrible, but I turned into like a skinless. Oh, wow
Really really
Joe so some people actually believe that they're actually real
What is this animal called? It's it's not a really animals called a
Something with a pussy. Oh, I want to know it's it's octopus
It's a platypus a platypus a platypus. It is a real animal. They're real
It really is really. Have you seen a platypus in person?
I haven't seen one in person, but I but I can tell you that they are real by everybody's
Yeah, I thought what do they look like now for a long long time
They thought that they were a fake animal like the jackalope, but actually then they got to Australia and found out no
There's a thing is a platypus
There's a thing of a panda bear and then I just I look closely and I was a it was a fat guy that got punched in the face
Oh, oh wow
The bear that looked like a bad guy they got but no it was a bad guy
They look like they got punched in the face. It looked like a panda bear
That's quite a no, it's not gamble. It's him
Really rough costume, you know
I
Does okay. Well, that's him. I hope you kick him out if it's Brandon cuz I'm sick of it. I mean
Working is working
Yeah, yeah
Wait a minute, I was looking at comment. Oh there you go
No, it's Gamble. It's a real Gamble. This is a count.
Gamble, you're welcome to come up and talk to us.
I think...
Make sure it's not him.
Put any of the hand.
I will. I'm going to look at this picture backstage.
And I need to see him flex backstage.
No, Gamble goes along to come up.
That's not me.
Well, then who is it?
It's probably his brand.
You've got to be so confused.
Yeah, see?
That's how crazy he is.
That's what he realizes.
Damn. He's in the Q Army.
I was putting in a bunch of hot guys in uniform,
in military uniforms.
Of robots robots in a bunch of bots like gamble said see he keeps trying we're not even talking about him
He's he's insane. He's trying to make it all about him
Everybody knows about him guys, you know Richard Shadiner Richard Shadiner went into a rocket and save this live because
Gamble needs to see this and see that he's over there trying to make alts on him. That's sick
It's just go home
Shut up because we're not even talking about you get some help
I mean you're on hinge and you need mental help
I mean and lie and lies and doesn't have prove but I'll show all our texts and show the prove
I've never said anything about hurtin anybody and that's what he does and you'll be
I'm gonna let you talk for a second. If you can like pull three cards for that'd be so awesome
I don't have my cards with me
channel for
Well, let's see what
What is your issue do you have an issue? Hello, where did you go what who?
You thank you
Somebody's recording somebody's recording him for me because I'm gonna go ahead and make a report
I mean, oh, okay crazy
I should have known better because I knew then he was bad news because I saw KK post
Okay, I see a rose over your head. I see it burst into flame
there's a
Okay, there is an owl there. There is somebody who's knowledgeable, but also deceptive
The rose that burst into flame that's kind of an odd thing to see over your head
I'm not quite sure what that means yet. Maybe it'll come to me later
The flaming rose the rose well the rose
has is the same thing as the Lotus has the same basic meaning as the Lotus may have something
to do with that and what's over your head is like what's crowning it it's like what uh
let me see what you're standing on and who is this person over here okay what are you standing on
you're standing on a pillar of it looks like a pillar of
stone, but under that is like air. It's like air wind holding you up. There must be an
air sign involved in something. Either you're an air sign or something is supporting you that is like
of air, that would be, the correlation would be swords. That would be mental energy. Okay,
so mental energy being expended, in which case the rose being on fire, that's the lotus.
Wait, wait, wait. There's another one that owl. Okay, there is somebody in your energy
that is
Deceptive, although they know a lot, okay? They are wise in some ways, but they're also can be deceptive
And you have to be careful not to let them blindside you. This is gonna be at night
Okay, this is going to be at night time because they're a night owl. So there is some night owl that is
Not
It's not that they're unfriendly exactly. They're just sort of tricky and they like
Like to mislead you
Okay
I'm still trying to figure out exactly what's going on with the with the rose with the flame
I think it has something to do with
Censalotuses, like a chakra.
That's usually associated, I think,
the rose one is high heart.
Yes, high heart.
Well, you know what?
That's very interesting.
If that chakra is burning,
You might want to clear out your heart chakra
It's it's almost like something is trying to affect your heart in
Inflame your heart
Let's see which way is that going is that going in a positive like
Flaming heart or is that
negative
I'm trying to see it
Are you still there?
I'm here. Can you hear me? Okay? Yeah
so
Basically
I'm hearing the black dog song got a flaming heart can't get my fill, okay?
Okay, so there is some kind of drama going on in your life that
Is my life or his life?
You know your life
Some kind of a deception at night that takes place with a night out. Okay. That's probably him then what is
Right. I'm not up late at night anymore. Like I used to be so no
So that's just talking about this thing here
Yeah, that the high heart you you really cannot let this
affect your heart chakra which it is it's affecting your heart chakra it's not
good for you yeah it's sick that's why I'm I'm getting away from it and all he
doesn't need to do is apologize to that person that he keeps going in her
chats about money you know that's fucked up
That's why I cut it off and and wait, you know, if he continues to wait for what happens because I'm gonna go ahead and
This is not good for you. You really got to stay out of this. No. Oh, yeah
I'm trying to
You're trying to jump on the panel, but then stay out because oh, yeah, I did
Everywhere physically this line affecting you physically
You're gonna get everybody else
Yeah, no, I'm not gonna let me let it get get me sick
I should have just never helped me out because I knew everybody told me that he's bad news and there I was
I did it for her and I thought
And he seemed cool in the beginning, but there he's acting like like the guy that we see on those videos
Now there's some kind of green little gremlin over to your
Mmm, that would be
May, no, that'd be on the female side, there's some kind of a green grim, like a, not, now
that creature is just mischievous, not really evil, but it's a female, it's a relatively
young person.
Yeah.
Real young or younger younger than me. Well, just younger than you and smaller
Okay
Kind of a younger person. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, okay. I know female. Yeah
Kind of a little gremlin. Okay
That's not as bad as this this may be
No, no, this is just
Yeah, this is not as this is not threatening really this is just a little yeah, I'm not remlin
Okay, that's that's no that's no biggie
Yeah, it's not like the person trying to deceive you. Yeah, there's more going on with that person
And then it looks like then meets the eye. I'll see
Something is hidden there and let me see what else is going on
Um
I'm seeing something weird here, but I can't figure out what it is saying and let it come in clear
Okay, there's a friendly dog
Okay, that usually means yes, I'm yours. Why either a loyal friend or a literal dog
No, it's my dog. It's my pinky knees
Oh, okay. Hello, baby. You coming in, mommy's reading.
His name is Nicholas. Oh, he's looking.
That's such a vibe from Nicholas. Nicholas.
That's such a vibe for me. You know what I'm about.
He's like, looks there and like confused.
Nicholas.
Yeah, you coming in your mommy's reading I can feel you know, I can feel your good dog
Yeah, I usually do attract the people's pets
It's funny. Yeah, I get psyches cats. Sometimes it's funny. Oh, really? Yeah, I've heard Teresa
She has a cat that sometimes just wants to come up and talk to me. So
I have four rescues
He worries about you. Yes, he does. Yeah
And he comes over worries about you
And that's why he's an emotional support.
He is an emotional support dog.
Yes, he is.
Yeah, he knows what his job is.
Yeah, he does.
Like one time I was triggered by on the phone
with somebody like this guy and he came and, you know,
and he was, I think he was human before.
He was like, you know, just wind it up in my lap
and look up at me and he was so cute.
You know there is my cat my my cat's even
Cuz they can tell if I get upset like that they come over to be you know. Yeah
Yeah cowboy is brilliant cowboy is actually my cat
He is really brilliant and I am so lucky. Yeah, he's a rescue and
He absolutely loves belly rubs
Yeah, and they do
My cat does though
Well, what a couple of them do but the bully cat. I've never tried again. It's like you know, sometimes
Yeah, a lot of times cats don't and the reason they don't is it tickles it tickles
No, it literally tickles they want you to love them, but that's why they let you they stick out their belly
They're showing trust. Yeah, and they want to be loved, but then it tickles
And I don't grab them because it tickles they told me that they told me it starts to tickle and then they just
Instinct takes over and they grab your hand
You know, so yeah, I'm so lucky.
I'm so lucky.
He likes belly rubs.
It doesn't tickle him too much.
Like my dog.
It's not ticklish.
And he is he's almost like a dog that way.
He wants his belly rub all the time.
Yeah. Oh, really?
You like belly for a freaking hour.
Like the youngest one she loves it. He'll lie there and purr. Yeah, you'll lie there and purr, purr, purr
Like a little motorboat the whole time for an hour if your arm doesn't fall off, right?
So yeah, yeah, he's great. I love mine. My cowboy
I was thinking I have one cat
that I took in and me and a neighbor share them because one of the bully cats still gives them a hard time sometimes
And that's a place for him to go to get away from her and then he'll come back over here and feed him and he's ill-breathed, he'll sleep.
And we haven't named them yet and I'm just calling boy cat right now
I wouldn't expect you to take in another can't probably come do what his name needs to be
But you know what it's like to come to you for a reason they always do
Yeah, he keeps coming over here and and that neighbor has a couple of kids and you know
He keeps coming over here knowing
My that bully cat
Still has an issue and and you know, and then she hides and she's upset with me
You know like she just doesn't want her you know him to show up again
Okay, the Robin
There is no Robin
And it's him again. He's crazy. You know what I am gonna do a police report on him
I didn't really realize he's this sick. We're not even talking about him
So my god, this is he's insane. Yeah, there's blocking. He just he's insane
I don't want nothing to do with them. I've been through this twice. He made threats. I didn't make threats about anybody like that
He's a liar, but wait till I show everything if he just leaves me alone
Get lost and apologize to Alex. That's all he needs to do because that's that's going too far that you're over there demanding her to
Give 1,000 and then 2,000 and that's why she's going to everybody. Are you talking dollars or what? Yeah, yes
Yeah
The red Robin is him. That's him
What's he he's
Then he's got mental issues to be making all these these also counts and bots
mean that's insane though you know what I've noticed that that a lot of these
people they just make it like a thousand bots and that's him yeah using bots to
be in his chat they said and they don't answer you they'll say one thing and
that's it and then another bot shows up and then when you
Say something to the first but they don't answer and again will show that to me. He said that's why they don't answer
Well, you know what this is how some people do it and I'll tell you how some people do this
And you can do this with several devices if you have several devices
you can make a person on each of your devices and usually what I would get would be in my in my chat
there would be three troublemakers right one would be first and then another and then another
there would be three and what that was was somebody on a phone somebody on a tablet and somebody on a
desktop or laptop right that but it was all the same person
Okay, and they would even sometimes start fights with each other.
Are you here with each other?
They can talk at the same time.
Our purpose is to be disruptive. Yeah, they'll do that.
No, I knew this guy who actually had this thing called the Army of Darkness where he had...
over a hundred personas that he could bring into a chat and he's had ways of
bringing them in and having them and he would have them just entirely disrupt
a chat room, arguing with himself, trying to get somebody else to throw into the argument.
And then just totally take over the show and disrupt it, take over the chat and disrupt it.
And that was his whole game. That was his whole game. He called it his army of darkness. Yeah.
So this guy needs to let it alone do real life. What's wrong with you? I mean
Right, can you imagine you're you're lucky, you know
Boyfriend or something you hadn't yeah, he doesn't have that make love or something maybe
48-year-old version or virgin
Yeah, but I mean, you know, maybe it's just a virgin
You know, all I did was block him he can't stand what we just I don't need this shit. I don't need this shit
You know, I'm done with the past
Well, and
It's just stupid that he keeps on and on and his 24 hours. It's it's YouTube and this and that and just messy and I
Have every single text their communication within from
From IG and in the text to the text now. I have everything. I'm so the you know
I am so over this that I just block me too
Yeah, and I blocked them everywhere
I'm up. I just block them again
Yeah, and I did that and that's why he's doing this
He doesn't leave people alone like gamble yet gamble haven't talked about him for a long time
And she keeps on and on with the same thing and he's just getting more haters
And everybody the whole communities are hating on him because they're saying that and they you know
Told me are you stupid? Do you not know?
I didn't know until Gamble sent that video and I looked at it today
And that's the same guy that we see that's all paranoid and all
Enhinged it's like get over it do real life
Mm-hmm. I mean it's all about the real life thing is go out touch grass give me in the sunlight
Get rid of your definitely white power and then clump and that guy clumsy who she said that he pulled up on
True that he didn't pull up at his place. He didn't live last night and he showed his place
And he showed that he was pretending to be at his place when he was in his own neighborhood. Oh
Brother and everybody saw that everybody was like wow. What is it go?
And he showed where he was because if you pulled up you would have seen this, the yard, the brick sidewalk.
Yeah, it's just insane that he does this and he didn't go over there to Clovis because we were waiting on him that we're going to go live some place.
And he said he was going to come on and then all of a sudden the person that was waiting to go live.
All of a sudden he disappears and I said,
look, where are you?
You said you were gonna do it at this time
and the person only has 30 minutes.
He was gone only 30 minutes.
So there's no way she made it to Clovis from Albuquerque
because I remember we drove to Clovis
for our football championship game when I was in high school.
And that's a long drive.
That's not, you know, I mean, it's not a short drive.
It's somebody it's sick go that far. I mean, it's yeah the fake it to fake it
That's really weird man, you know, and and he says he doesn't dox. He's doxing all these people like that clumsy
I mean, it's ridiculous something about a kid's picture was posted. Why are you posting pictures of kids?
I don't want anything to do with you Brandon. Please leave me alone. Okay. I'm making it clear. I'm done with you
Go apologize to Alex. This is ridiculous. You're doing this to everybody. You go nuts and I'm tired of it
We had one that would just go to everybody's show and fm up somehow
Mm-hmm. There's something he'd be nice at first then he'd turn around and stab you in the back
and he only did it with one because he'd come and he'd apologize and people would come up to me
oh but he's just trying to be he's got a mental issues and he's got this you know and it's like well you know what it's like I cannot
I don't have time to deal with that I'm not getting paid for this and I'm certainly getting hurt by it if I let him do it again
Yeah, and I saw that vegan Patriot live where he was trying to take advantage of her and she was sleeping and then he lies
Oh, I talked to her. No, he doesn't talk to her. She she said something and you know denied everything
He claims he's in his mind. He thinks she's her his girlfriend
Needed a place to crash out at I used to talk with her and she told me about that at that time
and then she needed a place to crash.
And I saw that video and it was sickening
that he kept fucking with her and he wouldn't let her sleep.
She needed sleep and she had her dog
and he kept putting his hands on her
and trying to kiss her and say,
say you love me.
I mean, it's sick.
And I would see that before.
I was staying at this guy's place one time
and his roommate didn't like it
and his roommate would not let me sleep.
Was so cruel.
Yeah.
Do anything do not let me sleep, you know, and you know what? I've never met an unhinged person like that in real life
never
People really but no like him. I mean it's completely out there. I'm talking about that. It's okay
But boy, I've met a few really talking people. He stalks everybody when you're done with him. I'm done
I gave him one more chance
This guy we call that he called himself puck elf then he had another one that was called spite fairy
It was still him
Personality
Yeah, you're gonna be sick to keep doing alt after alt after alt
And I finally said no you're not coming back. No, I don't care what your story is
Sorry to hear about that and he was so mad at his parents. He was so so emo
So mad at his parents and he wasn't a young guy. He was an older guy and I said, do you know what?
I did a reading and he wanted a reading from me
I did a reading from him for him and I did it for nothing
Okay, I would you know because at first he was nice. I said, okay. Well, what's your trouble?
Well, you know, my parents they don't really love me. They don't really care about me
I just feel so you know and he went online. Okay. Okay. Let me look
and I pulled a card because I do like cards sometimes I'll like get out and be doing a card
everybody gets a card a piece and I pulled the card out and I said
It says here that your parent, and I forget what the card was, but it was like your parents are doing their best. Okay. Your parents actually love you. They're doing their best, but they don't know what to do with you.
And he goes, that's not true. That's not true. You know, and he was just so all up in his feelings about his parents and how terrible they were to him and everything.
But really when I got to know him later what happened with him was he was just so random and so
Multiple personality that you couldn't keep up with him and probably his parents were there like
You know who that's
They said that he wasn't with his parents he was actually grew up with his uncle or something
I don't know there these people try to send information. I don't even know if they were his real parents or anything
His parents ended up passing on and he was like absolutely
Devastated
It's sad when you lose your parents.
I'm there like, dude, now you understand, now you get it.
They actually were looking out for you more than you thought.
You thought they weren't doing anything.
Yeah, and then you remember the good things about both parents.
I adored my mom.
And it really hurts.
She was very young when she had me.
So she was mostly.
Are you going to be careful?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, that's right. That's why I don't need this. It's like go back off and just leave me alone. I'm done
I mean he went it went too far over there demanding money a second time and I didn't even catch the one about the
Money for what? I know Ryan. It's like who do you think you are that that's extortion and and and me and
What did he do did he
Is somebody
Yeah, it's like who do you think you are to demand money from from somebody it's like are you crazy?
He's you know, he doesn't get it and he keeps on and on and on. I'm telling you that's insane a
Normal person would just leave it alone and and that's that not try to make new numbers
Well, you know what? It's like you see recording and everything is it's recorded on my calls
Well, there's no need to feed into it anymore though really right like yeah, I'm trying not to
but uh if i have this is like a type of energy vampirism all that's it it's a type of energy
vampirism and he doesn't even give people time to calm down i mean like the other day when he
said kill yourself because he said i was defending brandon because they gave me that video and he was
Ah, you know kill yourself fuck you, you know, and then I gave him a chance
I was flipping out and and it won't happen again and there he is going nuts because he's the one that was in her chat again
You know demanding $2,000 and she's blaming me and psyche along with him. I didn't know
Charge out of it. It energizes him. He is siphoning energy when he does that
And your own your defense has got to be
Absolutely. No, no, and I mean it. No and from here on
No more mention no more telling him. Yeah, let's not mention him. No
No, I don't mention him. He's the one that he wants it all about him sick. Yeah, it doesn't
Trying to suck up all the energy
Mm-hmm. That's what he's doing. We're gonna turn it to something else, right?
Because you got a good dog and you like rescue, so do you rescue a lot? Yeah, I do rescue.
Yes, mostly cats. Me too. I used to do a lot of rescue. Really? And I have a friend that used to run a big rescue, but I don't know what happened to her.
you know something pills and she abandoned a dog with him and so he was letting people know hey
you know she's in a bad space right now back to doing that um what was that um she wasn't abusing
illegal drugs it was like prescription drugs and then she was never on the calls when people
You know so now we do it on our own over here and we work together and a lot of my neighbors help
And they've gotten involved and I do have a call to come pick it up from them to take him to the vet and
I and
two others pay for it or me and
So they take care of them and then they bring him back
So that's why they're helping because I gave everybody texted them the information
call and you know they'll pick him up in the morning and bring him back by two
o'clock because it's far it's very very far I gotta wait we had a place
around here
called pet guards. I don't know if we still have it, is it still running? But it was a
great animal sanctuary and it was a no kill facility and you would pay like twenty five
dollars or something and then to place the animal there and then they would actively
try and get your animal a home and it would not
be killed, it would not be euthanized.
Yeah, and it's hard to find that here now since COVID.
It's like the rescues now are so far away,
like too far from us, like not in Houston where we need it.
Well, it really made me sad is that
there was a place that was trying to take care of rescues.
They had a whole room of black cats.
Aw, they're heard, but the people give up, they're heard of them, and I'm like, oh my god.
All these cats or cats that people got rid of that just they were all
Beautiful to their and I'm like oh my god. I wish I could take every single one of them
Oh, yeah, that's that's the way I think when I see him
But now I've got a lot of support here and there's such sweet babies all of them
That's sweet babies
And all they wanted was just to be petted and loved. That's all they really wanted
And yeah, I mean mine are so I mean they're so sweet and and they're good
But people think they're they're evil because they're black cats. I've changed a lot of people's mind. I really have
Because I don't just don't understand cats. They are not dogs
That's not dogs. That's all there is to it. You cannot expect them to act like dogs.
But yeah, they are sweet in their own way. They're just different. And you have to just get all this
stuff out of your mind that you learned about dogs. And once you do that and realize they're just an
entirely different animal than a dog, then you can start to deal with them on their own terms.
And then they're pretty easy to understand.
They they like pretty much the stuff that people like.
They want love, they want food, they want shelter and they want a clean cat box.
And beyond that, they're really easy.
I mean, they want to play.
They like to play.
They like to sleep a lot.
They need like they do, right?
I mean, hours a day. Yeah.
My pecanese pecanese is that's a breed. My pecanese is they're like that. They're lazy
They'll they can sleep so much and they don't really need more much exercise. They say they're they're like cats
Yeah, that's why my cats love him
And they don't say that though, that when the cats, the cats can be like sleeping 18 hours a day and then they get up and they do all of these things that we'd love to be able to do and they're not doing crunches at the gym or anything.
They're not going to the gym or anything and they just.
You know, and I'm like, boy, that is so unfair, you know, right? Yeah, they're chill and lazy and they're good for, like, mostly adults, because sometimes they're not that great with kids.
Well, you know what, a lot of them know, though, kids, every cat we had, okay, we had a cat named Thurs, and he
Had his biggest fan was a little boy
My best friend's brother at little boy and he would come over and he just loved sirs and sirs would be there
sitting there like oh my god the kid but he loves me so I gotta sit here and let him you know and Michael would come over and give him a hug and he'd be like you know and he'd have his eyes closed and Michael would be fussing over him doing all this stuff and he'd be there just like okay okay it's a kid I can't do anything about this I'll just sit here and let him
Oh, it was so funny.
Oh, man.
And the little kid is watching the cat, right?
And the cat saw something on top of the fridge
that he wanted to look at.
And all of a sudden, the sirs.
kind of just up and just jumps on top of the
On top of the refrigerator, which is a pretty high right so the kid is looking at this
And this was back at the time
This was like way back during the time when there was the sixth million dollar man. You remember that show. Oh
Yes
So
And the kid looks at the cat jumping on it he goes
Six million dollar cat.
Oh, you're such a good cat.
Yeah.
So forever after,
this kid was the biggest fan of the six million dollar cat.
Oh my God, that's funny.
But they're beautiful. I love all animals. They're so cute. So he was like, oh, six million
dollar cat. I have to go hug him, you know, hug him and pet him. Here's a six million dollar cat.
Yeah, six million dollar cat. Imagine that. Every time. Yeah, I missed those days. That was when
a lot of
Right, and I heard somebody it wasn't long ago. He died and he left his home and
his whatever money that he had left over because he was
Alone, I guess and he when he passed away. He'd left that money for his cat and whoever
Could take care of the cat
Cat that home was the cat's name
You know what in his will
I think I would want,
I would probably leave it mostly to my cat to find a home.
Yeah, me too.
You know what?
Somewhere to be in, you know.
And my friends that helped me,
I don't have a family anymore.
I'm old enough that my family is gone.
My family has been.
As you go on, you know, you want to get two places.
mean I had the hardest time when it was my birthday and I realized it was the
same age that my mom was when she passed away and I had a hard time why am I here
because I didn't expect to live you know I did a lot of drugs in the past you
know ODG would have taken a lot better care of myself if I'd known I was gonna
last this long
Yeah, me either I was expecting to be dead and some people are surprised that I'm alive and I lost some friends that were younger than me like
My best friend Denise her cervical cervical cancer came back and
I went to Utah for a while and and a friend stayed at my place and when I got back
I think it was January it was a
2022 I think
came back and and then later I was I was opening my email and I see a message
from her daughter saying please call me because she didn't have my number and I
read it and she said mom you know that cancer came back and she's in the
hospital and that she was dying and she wanted to see me but couldn't talk
anymore she was that weak and I answered her
And then the next day she answered back and she said she's gone.
So, I mean, it was like a day later something and that was heartbreaking because she was my best friend and she was there when my mom passed away.
And she was so funny though. I used to I liked her since the humor and she was so sarcastic like when you'd say something stupid
You know, she'd say you know you did wrong
But the way she said it was
You know, you know, you did wrong or something like that the way she said it like this song
So you like you like the psyches videos, right?
I like the videos
I want to learn to make those I'm doing all right now. I'm doing one right now
See I have all these songs that I have written. I'm a songwriter among other things. Oh you are a songwriter
Wow and a singer. I was a singer for a
Um, actually, I, I have been an entertainer most of my life. Okay.
Really? That's great.
Yeah. And, um, so I did sing telegrams. I did, um, I was, uh, in choirs. I was, uh, you know, I did.
All through school. I did I did choirs. I did choirs on TV. You know, I
was gonna choir and
And and church church
I think I did a Chris's page and I was a I was a shepherd. I was shepherd number two. Oh
I did place. Yeah, I did place and I didn't play
I did sugar, which is a to some like a hot and I did I did a once upon a matches, which is um
Princess and the pea it's a more modern carol bird net was in it in the 60s or something
Oh really that
Yeah, I remember that
I want to show you I want to show you guys you like my music
because I want to show you what I want to show you I'm doing
like some my question to you. What are you using to make your
damn videos? Well, I'm doing videos. Thank you. I am. If
you don't answer me and I'll ask you but the video the video
generation I've been doing is from meta AI and it's free.
Basically, I mean, it's free. I just do it. Yeah. Okay.
sort of putting, it's called meta.ai.
It was a lot easier to use before.
Now you have to kind of do it one at a time,
you have to generate the images,
describe the image you want, or the video.
But it's free, but I'm gonna show you this
and see if you like this, okay?
This is my example of my horror.
Okay, I'm gonna ask you afterwards
about your nightmare in Elm Street experience,
but one second, here we go.
We now return you to your regularly scheduled sleep.
Please remain horizontal.
Please do not blink. Please do not count the others in your bed.
I love this music. Thank you.
I was a club DJ.
You were?
Awesome.
In college, in college, at St. Houston State University,
they had a club me and Eunice were DJs there,
and then later Club in Success in Houston, Texas, by the Galleria.
Awesome.
I was an internet DJ.
I was one of the very first internet DJs.
Yeah.
Me and a guy named Studer and he passed away, you know, he ended up passing away
Later on I realized that the people that were in the chat room were all from the people
Yeah, I only found it out later
That they were what? They were the... they were all very from the people
Oh, wow
Yeah
I was back to really
Doing the the music for all of these famous people and didn't even know it until later on they were incognito
Right, and one of them was David Bowie. Actually, that's how I struck up a friendship with David Bowie online. Oh, wow
He actually is funny what he was so funny people didn't realize that side of him
He had the greatest sense of humor
He was hilarious
he just had such a crazy sense of humor and
We we just kind of fed off of each other, but I could not
Come out to California. I had someone I I was married and
I was I was married once and then he got married too and then
So, you know, but we we had this
We had this weird relationship over, you know
In this chat room first and then and then it just kind of kept finding him online
I kept finding him again and again
It was really weird and then we'd realize and at first I didn't even believe who he was
I didn't even believe that that was actually really David Bowie
And then he started putting some things in his videos that we talked about and you know
The one blue Jean was when the the genie, you know, Aladdin
Blue genie. Yeah, he did that. All right, blue genie. Save me. Oh, yeah
Okay
Now
Anywhere he says she's got lilac lips. Yeah, you know, you know
Guess whose lips those were that he was talking about your lips exactly
That was mine because he asked me what shade my lipstick. He wanted to know what kind of makeup I used
because she used makeup. And I told him, I said, lilac really suits my skin the best because I have
kind of blue tones in my skin. And I actually used eyeliner for lip liner called lilac called
iced lilac. And he said, that's very interesting. That's a good idea. I said, well, it doesn't
I just think she got legs, she knows how to use them, D-Oceans, D-Oceans, this is my friend
on the screen, I'm just gonna show you real quick, he was shot three times in the chest
three months ago, but we were, but before he died,
He was like his star was shining bright. He was on a lot. She's a streamer, right?
He's streaming a lot, but I just want to play the, I played the song before he passed away to him personally.
Oh, before you do that, I wanted to let her know my mom was friends with Raquel Welsh, who was half Bolivian and half American like me.
And when she had plastic surgery done, she stayed at our house until she recovered.
And Ferrera, what was her name that she's running?
America Ferrera America Ferrera. No, this was in the 80s and she it was an older lady
And she had a son that had a cocaine problem and had to go to treatment and so that was brought up when she was in the running
And something Ferrara you'll find I forget her first name, but yeah, she she's half Bolivian
Yeah, something Ferrari she was running for like office here in the States and that's what Rock Hill did
She held like a convention for the people from Bolivia
People she knew and my mom was always there
And I have a strong like Native American energy from both you ladies
I guess you have a Native American
My mom no, no not native here white and actually even
German and Spain from my mom's parents
Spain they're there they're considered white Caucasian in Spain on my mom's side Cherokee
Oh, and the reason she did this Raquel is because she brought a female
From Bolivia that was running for office over there. So yeah, it was in Helden Conroe, too
Don't cry for me Argentina, right? That's what I'm thinking
But can you take this out real quick? This is my friend Danny. He passed away. I played the song for me
Oh, go ahead. Yes. Go ahead. I don't see this song. I wrote this. He heard the song
But I want to see if you get any vibes to eat from him, I want to just let me know. Thank you.
Oh, okay.
I'm acting normally and sure okay, but my brain's yelling open, I made your way
He did one little dance and my soul said fine, now I'm losing my dignity, one beat at a time
I don't hit him up much, I keep it tight, cause he's got that charm that can wreck my night
One smile on hate and I'm already sure, he'll talk me into something expensive
I want a box and a pack, you dance for me once now I'm down bad facts, but I'm keeping it casual while I'm losing my tracks
I know he ain't gay, so don't make it weird, I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear
I don't talk to him much, cause I know what he'll do, he'll talk me into buying him a whole dang truck
And I don't even ever back do
He got that I might be problem grand Like he's selling sunshine with a citizen
He laughs, I fold my wallet, get scared I'm tryna play cool, but I'm deeply unprepared
I'm not sayin' I'm obsessed Just molly the range like who needs self-respect
When the vibes is strange I keep my distance, I do my best
But he pops in my head like a bad text
He says we should hang, I'm like maybe soon
Then I hide in my house like a raccoon
Dantest stranger, your trouble, your cutie tag
I want up in your socks and a pack
You danced for me once, now I'm down bad facts
But I'm keeping it casual, I'm losing my tracks
And though we ain't gay, so don't make it weird
I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear
I don't talk to him much, cause I know what I'll do
You would talk me into buying him a whole dang truck
He'd never buy a goose
I'm a responsible adult allegedly
But that man says, babe, and my brain goes spend money
I'm not his bank, I'm not his plan
I'm just a humble fan with a morally questionable stance
If he blinks twice, I'm making poor choices
Hearing cash registers like back voices
You're trouble, you don't attack
You're wearing your socks in a bag
You danced for me once, now I'm down bad bags
But I'm keeping it casual while I'm moving my trap
Make it weird, I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear
I don't talk to him that much, cause I know what he'll do
He'll talk me into buying any more whole thing
I don't even have a bite to
Danny Stranger, please stop being adorable
My finances can't take it
I just want to say he was like I was on the show a lot recently even like before he passed away
I had my check over there. I didn't read his check. Yeah, his name is Danny Stranger
He was he was viral because he had a video with over a million views where he got fired from Walmart
like a few several years ago and
He was even in a weird video game on online like they use this stream
He's a streamer, but he went to a gas station. He was streaming three months ago almost to this day. Oh, wow
Yeah, how did he pass away?
How did someone in the gas stations
shot him three times in the chest?
Oh my God.
Oh my God, that's awful.
Yeah, it's awful.
It's awful.
But it's like right before he passed away,
he was streaming all the time.
And so I was there a lot.
While he was streaming, he went there and he was streaming?
Well, yeah, you can hear the gunshots on his last one.
Oh, good heavens.
Yeah, it's terrible.
That's awful.
He was a really cute guy.
He was always with,
but the song is about.
Yeah, he's cute.
Yeah.
I paid him like $30 once and he danced.
God, he was so young.
He was so young.
Yeah, he was like probably four years old
or something like that.
Wow.
But he would take, he'd have his shirt
and then I was like,
I would say I wanted to buy his wife beater.
We were negotiating the price at the time.
It went to, I wanted to pay $30 for it.
He's like, I paid $30 for this.
He wanted to charge me thousands of dollars for but you know RAP take take he was a sweet
He was a sweetest guy. He was really sweet like a really nice guy. Actually
He didn't deserve what happened to him. I he lived in Oregon or something like that and
Yeah, you know things happen sometimes, but you know
RAP Danny stranger that was a song but he didn't get to hear that song. I played for him
That was my little country song. So you can hear my example and I will teach you guys
I'll give you my method, but I'll teach you actually how to do your own method like I'll teach you how to just
Make you yeah, I want to learn to you better
I went into a program called soon. Oh
Yeah, I got something pretty good out of that. I'm working on this project called I don't break for zombies
No, I want to do a video with it, too
I've got the song I wrote the song a long time ago man Rudy this cat is set as 18 year old
I think he's 18 17 or 18 18 yeah, and they look young and then when they hit 20
I don't know if it's all cats with you
Because he comes on me and he just he's meowing a lot
Yeah, I am he's getting old, but yeah, I took him in last like last year in January
He's just rude. It's not a thing. Well, they they warned me. They told me that that probably happened, but she she was okay again and it's
Yeah, I mean they just mean it's like an older cat and and it's like blessings people that do that because they're our older animals of the shelter
Yeah, see the cowboy was another cowboy's an older guy. Yeah
Yeah, the one's missing most of his teeth now
Oh, well, you know mine had all her teeth, but
but she got lost one day when she's went out and she never got lost before that's it's how
and i found her finally a couple days later and she was fine and you know she just seemed like
she was forgetting things i had a fever by hand and the vet said you know she doesn't have much
And he thought, you know, he was just going to check her in a couple of months and then she passed on and I got great neighbors and
Management here. They were
Remember the rainbow bridge at this point like we do do know the rainbow bridge story, right?
Oh, cool. Yeah, my cat. I actually saw my cat
die. She actually, well, I'm a psychic medium. I'm a medium. You know, I heard they go, they,
yeah, they go a high drill dude, and then they pass away. You know, you should know what,
she didn't. She didn't. She wanted to be near me. It was, I was spelled so honored.
and mine didn't leave me either she was with me she was with me but she was just so slow and
you know like kind of telling me mine was blind by the time she died yeah but she drug her poor
little self up on the bed and she passed away right in front of i started seeing
All of these rainbow flashes all over the room. I wasn't feeling very good. Yeah, right
You feel him and you feel him like and white and white and I saw
And then I saw, I swear to God, I saw it look like a rainbow portal opened up.
I am not kidding.
It looked like a puddle.
It opened up and you could see somewhere else on the other side.
It was beautiful and green and my cat rose up.
She was like in Sphinx position and she rose up out of her body.
just so easy and she just walked through that portal and then she was on the other side and
I knew she was gone but you know what yeah but it was a beautiful place and she came back to visit
and she she talked to me quite often they do they do because years ago when my parents had
He was 17 years old and it was time and my mom said she was going to go to the vet, my dad too, and they wanted me to come with them, so we took her and they said they had to put him to sleep.
And my mom was crying and she said I can't be here for that to happen and my dad didn't want to be there
So I had to be the one in there
I wouldn't let him go like that by himself and I held on to him and then they gave him a shot
It was just hard, you know, and I was I had just gotten my first my own first two Piketty's puppies
I had him at home and I held them and it affected me, you know, and we went home in silence and my mom was crying and
I didn't cry. I was trying to hold it in. So finally, you know, when I get home and I had my two
Pekingese's and I put them on the couch and they were too small to jump off because they were puppies.
They were show quality. And so I went to the kitchen and I'm crying and I was trying to
And and I thought wait a minute. That's weird or one of the puppies out
How did they get down and I go look and they're sleeping on the couch
So I go back to finish. I'll feel it again
And I started crying because I remember Kai Chi used to do that to my mom
When she'd be getting her food ready. He'd always go in between her ankles
And when I was telling her she goes oh my god
That was Kai Chi because he loved you and you were the one there with him
Because what would he be doing? He'd be there to let her know. But yeah, I felt him. And I don't know, it was just so weird. It was...
You know, really, your pets often come back. I find that that happens with a lot of people. Their pets often come back, whether they notice it or not, I think they always come back.
They do!
Like the first peeking is that he had cancer and my parents didn't let me know that they were taking him to put to sleep
We were in school and he was a year older than me and he thought I was his baby
Because he'd sleep under my crib and he'd growl at anybody trying to come in I was hit and
When he they took and I didn't know I came back you know what a lot of time we don't have pets some of us
Don't have pets. We have guardians
And so that day I was crying and they put him to sleep and I was just you know kind of upset like why didn't you give me a warning he was a year older than me so he was part of our family and he was like my my guard dog and I remember when we go to the basement they had a pool table and stuff for us kids and we played down there.
This was in Overland Park, Kansas.
And I remember I had his chain that I kept
and my mom gave it to me and that's kept it
in my room upstairs in my door.
And I remember everybody with us kids,
it's like, we'd hear that chain rattling
like he was there, but he never spent time in the basement.
Him or the other Piketty's.
But I thought, am I hearing things?
But everybody else was like, wow,
that sounds like Chico's, his nickname was Chico.
Chico's chain and and I don't know that was weird too. Like was that him or were we hearing things?
But it sounded like it was chain and I went to my room. Probably it was looked in the drawer
And I saw that the chain was there and it was like that was confusing. It's like that was the only sign
About this I wrote actually I have many stories of my animals coming back
but people to and people to but
Um, there's a song I wrote called Believe, and it's, it starts out, um,
Can you see me? Do you hear me? I am right by your side.
I still love you.
I didn't want to leave you, but it's hard to be denied.
Did you know that love can last forever, even in the afterworld?
love you and you will always be my girl yeah it's a beautiful song that is a
beautiful song I want to put that I want to animate that song I want to record it
and animate it that's why psyche is being mean and not even happen
I got it. Can you put it? Can you put her channel link in the chat so I can click and sub to her?
To Ocean
It's the ocean Steve Wu
the ocean the oceans deep blue the oceans deep blue blue okay yeah it's kind of long but there's a
but okay yeah deep blue is what we do we do the deepest blue but I also sing during the show I
sometimes I sing sometimes I do cards sometimes we just shoot the bull sometimes I just
Tell you what I'm seeing for the next month or, you know, it's just something different all the time.
I just do something different.
Sometimes I'm telling you about the latest supplement I found or sometimes I'm reviewing something or, you know, it can be a lot of things that I do.
Sometimes I get out the pendulum.
Oh, that gets weird when I get out the pendulum.
and we start asking the pendulum questions.
Do you know, this was the weirdest thing.
During the time that when Biden was running against Trump,
I asked it, I said, okay, who's gonna win, Biden or Trump?
I said, okay, so, mm.
I but you have to state it in the positive terms, you know, you know, okay
So Biden wins and it said yes. So I said, oh then Donald Trump is gonna lose and it said no. I
Said what I said, okay, wait a minute. Let me try this differently
Donald Trump is gonna win. Yes. Oh, then that means Biden is gonna lose. No
Wait, wait, wait, wait, what's going on here?
So let me ask it another way.
Donald Trump is going to be president, yes.
But that means Biden is not.
And it's like, no.
Biden is going to be president?
Yes!
Wait a minute.
How can Donald Trump and Biden be president?
No.
And then we had all of that weird stuff over the election and the election being stolen
and everything.
And I'm there going, you know what, according to my pendulum, there was something very weird
going on during that election.
And I had never seen it do that in my whole life before.
And I asked my guys and they said.
Sometimes you have to realize that we're heading into a time when things that seem like they are mutually exclusive can actually both be true at the same time.
And I'm there like that's mind blowing and very deep and they said you'll get used to it.
It's so freaking crazy.
Look at how crazy our politics have been.
I mean, yeah, and all kinds of shit has been just so crazy
And it's like you think you got a handle on it and it just turns around and it's something else
Yeah, I can't find a channel
um, let me see
If I can type it in you're in the show, so I'll type it in here in the chat in the oh, okay
I go ahead and finish. So what do we say?
Sorry good
So basically, um, deep, okay, it's like this, the oceans, it's spelled like that.
And if they won't let you find it, I'll have to find it, you know, myself and
let's see if I can find it, get to my channel without losing.
was that is a cat is that a cat is that a capital do and then I'm sorry just a capital D and the rest in lower case
OCE a NSD
EP
WOO
Okay, I don't know if we lost her but here okay, I'm gonna
And the backstage for you
Ocean channel I got it for everybody here we go
You make sure to ocean and you if you guys if you don't behave at oceans channel. I'll kick your ass. Yeah
She has a strap. She has she has she has a
It's made of a little cow leather. I mean you have
Banking mechanism
Yeah, and so no one's gonna fuck with oceans and that is the real Joe shipply Joe
You're welcome to come up because Joe wants to ask a question before you go woo because you know Joe
So Joe's a ginger. Yeah, have you been for are you familiar with these ginger human human beings?
Yeah, ginger. Yeah, they're gingers. I mean, I mean should I consider the devil or should I give them a chance?
I can't figure it out yet
Well, you know when I was younger my hair was more red than blonde
So give juniors a chance, but only if they can prove that they do have at least partial ownership of the single-brain cell
Yeah, well, I saw his pubic hair. He does have like a it looks like it looks like a bag of Cheetos in there
So I think you look like a bag of Cheetos now wait a minute
It's like that powdered it's like the really bright orange color, but it's oh my god
Yeah, there's there's a link for grateful. Did you like grateful? I think you like I think you like people grateful
It's sweet. Okay, so you're a person. She's a rat. Okay cat rescuer. You're you're a dog
Do you have a rescue? Oh, here. Oh, we have a we have a Karen's back one second
Sorry about that. I was trying to
Copy that link and I dropped off. Okay. Go ahead and play the song. It's pretty I
Do that. You know what? I'm afraid too that I'm gonna drop off of the of the show
You guys heard of this song called
Have you heard of this a cartoon it's called the has been hotel. I mean it's no, okay
So the queen of hell or the princess of hell
is like, you know, she has a heart.
And so she's like, I want all the beings of hell
to be recuperated.
I mean, she says she wants to start a hotel
to kind of like, you know, to redeem everybody.
So she's a good heart.
I mean, her father's Lucifer, mother's Lilith, you know?
I mean, it's not always the easiest group of parents to have,
but I'll just talk about the whole.
Yeah, go ahead, go ahead guys.
I'll find in a second.
You guys talk for a minute, I'll be right back.
Okay, yeah, you can finish what you were you were saying something. It was nice when we were
Oceans, uh, what was it? I forgot no, right?
I forgot I think you were talking about
Oh, yeah, I got sidetracked and we got sidetracked. I know me too, because I dropped off on the phone.
Oh, look a kitty. You know what, I've come to the conclusion that cats are just natural.
ADD, you know, it's like, oh, look a kitty. But anyway, cats are just...
They just get they're beautiful because I remember my mom didn't like cats and I was a little kid. One of her friends had a cat and
And and you know her friend didn't she wasn't even loving to the cat or anything
She acted like she was scared because one time she came over and she had a patch on her eye
My mom asked her what happened and she saw that cat scratch me and when we went over to her place that cat is like
Like had no love or you know, he was just there that she fed
And my mom said don't don't go to that cat Karen because he's he's gonna scratch you and all and I love animals over people
So I went over there and sat with him in the kitchen
And he sat there just looking at me and then he came closer and closer
And then he let me pet him and I put him on my lap and my mom's friend when she came to the kitchen
She goes oh my god. He's never done that with anybody
I was weird if my mom said
You know, they've got etiquette cats have a natural
This is how the quiet person who doesn't want to be bothered by a cat ends up getting the cats attention
Because cats are not real forward with people. They don't know or animals. They don't know see to them dogs are very rude
Yeah, there's animals. Oh, yeah, my animals do talk to me from time. They explain some things
Animals explain a lot of things to me that I didn't understand
And and there's a lady on IG and she's I don't know what country she's in. She's in Germany. Oh, yeah, let's see this
And she shows her cat on IG
But we're already past that phase
This is a brand new start
And I think I deserve some praise for the way that I am
Despite having overdosed and ending up comatose
I don't give a damn
I've let my emotions go, fuck being a sober hoe
This is the mantra, this is my life
You're playing with now till the end of the night
To round it by fire, the passion ignites
I'm addicted to the madness
This hotel is my lanness
We're forever gonna have a fucking reason to sin
Let me leave my soul to burn it
I'll be breathing it in
I'm addicted to the feeling
Getting higher than the ceiling
And we're never
I don't want this fucking feeling done
Just concede and give and do your little demons again
But you fell deeper in this pit
Wild on my butt
So count your blessings cause this is it
You're not letting it go
So what if I misbehave
It's what everybody craves
You already what you like
We could have it all
Yeah, that's that's cool. I like that as well. Seriously. I love it. I got to say yeah
That was edgy as hell. I hope you post those videos
I don't know. I heard a cat meow. Who is that? Is that a cowboy or is that what a grateful scouts?
What? I don't know. I'm a minor too.
No, I got meowing. Did you want to see the Lenore? Oh, the Norse had it oceans. They're Bonnar quiet
Showing off her best side that's
Lookin' with the single eye!
No, it's the open eye.
It's the one with the eye, okay.
That's why the cats are the Illuminati,
because they're always the open eye, right?
There you go.
I was going to do it in the chat.
I don't know why Joe didn't come up.
Joe is scared of beautiful women.
Joe, because you're a ginger.
I know.
Joe, Joe should we?
Joe you like Joe Shippley
You left us there one night and you were gone. It's like we were there
Disappeared
you notice this and then you'll have a panel of people come up and they'll all be arguing and
you'll just say okay i need some money i'm gonna go out and get some td you'll go out and argue
for like an hour or two i mean i gotta eat i mean i have to eat too i mean and then you'll
come back in and they're still arguing but but but he didn't come back and yeah so it ended
man is you just get a bunch of people up here that argue with each other and it's like
No, there's no argument actually joe was cool
You guys are cool too. You guys I left you guys alone and as I came back and you were just talking
Yeah, we were just talking nicely to each other. Oh my god. What a concept
We can talk nicely to each other
Right yeah, it was a good combo because I didn't know much about him
I just saw that sometimes would go up people, but yeah, he was cool
You know what you guys are like you guys are awesome, and it's like you guys are
This is real. Fun, friendly, happy conversation, interested in the spiritual world.
Like, I mean, there's so much...
Interested in other people too, besides our fucking self, that's another thing.
It's all about being my problems and my shit, you know, it's like...
Animals, animals in our pits.
Animals, we love animals, we love magic, so...
Yeah, that's what I was saying to Ian next to me, I was like, you know what, it's like the people that have the hearts for the animals and the, you know, saving animals and they're the best hearts in the world, because sometimes they've been like animals more than humans, because humans are kind of like almost act worse than even the worst animal humans can be.
Right, right, yeah.
Well, you know, the weirdest thing is.
is whenever you rescue any living thing,
you're really more likely to get bit by the human.
Right, oh my God.
It's true, it's true, right?
It's almost right.
I do not understand it,
but I mean, I've taken in strays of every type,
and basically the human is the one
that's probably gonna bite you.
And I mean, not maybe physically, but you know.
That's true, the human.
I had a dog named yonko because the dogs and the cats are all grateful for you know being loved right yeah
The humans are you know, you're lucky if the humans don't walk away with happier shit and then smear your name
Or something, you know
Humans can have they can be like, you know more
Homicidal more evil
Like, you know the way they all that kind of the evil thoughts that come the human animals are basically they react to their
whatever's happening at the
love them and you feed them and
you know, take care of them.
They're so happy and they love
you and you know, they'll just
be the best thing ever. And
the best friend. I know.
What the hell is wrong with us?
Right? You know what?
That's it. Yeah.
You know what my dad said to me before he passed on but he said it to me like a few years before that it was weird
He I'd take my dogs with me everywhere and we went to go visit him and yell mean
He was a young dog and he was sitting on the couch just staring my dad because my dad was starting to get Alzheimer's
And he used to put him in his lap and play with him, but he was kind of not remembering and
and you know, Jeming would stare at him like, and my dad would say,
why is he staring at me? It's because he was trying to get his attention,
like, who are you right now? Because you always make a big fuss over me and he was concerned.
And my dad said then, and the time before, he said,
you know what, Karen, your pecan uses
are the most well-behaved pecan uses
because they raised a lot of peaks.
And what do you do to make them so calm
and they're not barking or anything?
And I told him, I'm not doing anything.
These were my babies.
And then he said it before that too.
So that was a compliment.
They mean more to me than humans.
You know, it's sad because I mean, human life is precious, however, it's a heck of a lot easier to live with my cat than anybody I ever lived with, right? Any roommate I ever had.
No, no abuse from an animal. They protect you.
They protect you. That's why I love them so much. Yep, and they don't they there's just so many things
Oh, they'll never steal your shit. They're old. They'll never they'll never break your
They'll only ever break your heart one time, right? It has to
One time and that's the day that they die that then your heart will be broken
And that that's what I'm ready to go
Last these guys go. I'm ready to go. I'm only here for them
So, you know what it's like there but there they came here for a temporary time and a temporary life
Yeah, they didn't get you did they get a kid in get it get a little puppy and
from a rescue or something and then continue to to help them improve their lives and then it's oh yeah
legacy you're not always you're always going to keep doing it joe came out of the yeah i keep
we keep doing that see now humans are weird aren't they they know that we all as pet owners every one
of us knows
They're going to die before we are probably I know that's what sucks and it's going to break our heart into and it's going to be horrible.
And we're going to hate it. However, we keep doing this over and over again because the joy in the meantime is so.
Good the love that we get from them is so good
The rainbow bridge when we go over the bridge
And then all the animals that we loved over our whole life are all they're waiting
Cuz we're there who are there's you know, it's like they we were their number
Oh, yeah, we're there. I should share that video of the rainbow bridge with with a bunch of dogs going up the steps to meet their
It's a beautiful, it's a beautiful, it's a beautiful
thought, beautiful story, but it's also, I believe it is true that when we pass.
I should do a video when Psyche finally gets around to helping me.
Yeah
Anyway, I should do one about my cat going through the rainbow bridge. I should do one like I have one
I have one uh
I g that's not my friend Nancy made for me and it was uh, one of my uh,
Old piquines is it passed away?
Um, you know the rainbow bridge. She did a rainbow bridge
post. Yeah, I should do that
I still have it
that is a real joke because Joe also had a dog Joe's dog with him and Raven and Raven passed away
and Joe still Joe still can't get another dog or he's still heartbroken by the dog but I believe
that someday Joe will get a puppy and it's like we need a dog arrest you arrest my you know what
though I think it's my thing it recently uh to have a second hand cat and an older I think we
We need to adopt and rescue
Older rescue mostly rescue
Older pets because they do not get taken people will take the kittens and the puppies
but they will not take the older pets a lot of times. They get passed over.
We're saying second hand and cat because sometimes people pass away with an older cat
and their family won't take the cat. Sometimes there's cats that are just on the streets until
they're very old. That's what happened to Cowboy is the owner passed away and the family didn't
want him and he was he was heading for the bound. If I want to pass away one month, my life would be
Yeah, I mean that's I mean that's what I'm saying. It's like it's like there are older cat
There's a second-hand cat side of the other just something passed on thing
It's like the second-hand cats is that the owner passed away or the cat like someone will end up without the owners
In somewhere another and we need to take in any any cats of me and it's like that's the hardest thing because we know
It's just like me with Rudy. No, we're not gonna have them for very long like short time. Yeah, however
Yeah, however, they are so grateful, so grateful, so loving that because they know
the two youngest cats I have or they're the black cats that were feral cats and uh they their mom
mom wasn't around one came running to me with and fell in love with my pygmy's y'all mean
and I have pictures of the first day because the guy that I was with took a picture of them
and the cat was on top of my peeking knees.
And yeah, they're beautiful.
And now one of them grew up and became a bully
and she thinks I'm all hers and she gets jealous
of the other cats, except she's okay with the baby,
but she thinks I'm all hers.
Right.
Cats will do that.
They'll pick out a person and then you're theirs.
It's like, dang.
you know what it's it's money dogs have owners but uh cats have owners yeah they're they think
they own you they're like uh this is my human thank you
Yep, then I have to show you real quick. So this is like
The short clip, but this is like when you know, these these ducklings and they I don't know
But you check out these ducklings with this cat right here
It's you'll love this these ducklings following this cat like it's their mom. Look at this shit. Look at this is great
Oh, you showed that. Yeah, long time ago.
I've seen this one.
She adopted a bunch of ducklings or loves their mom, yeah.
aww
you know what I'm trying to do
in front of the cat
there's like regular ducks
in the water
all up or down
oh my god
don't get up here
I just like to go
I don't
I think
I'm a buddy
Hurry and funny looking, but she sure is good doing it.
I love my yellow babies.
Just as much as anything.
Look at the cats on this one.
The cat is so...
Yeah.
They stop right behind me.
They're just like, so...
Good, good.
Look at the cows, though.
There's a head print in the first one.
Look at the cow.
I've been getting into these teas that I've been getting online and I found this wonderful
tea called milk oolong and I have never had this happen with a tea before but I made a
cup of this tea and it smells it's very strange at first it smells like cream and then gradually
Porn a cornfield and a pastor and I'm there and all of a sudden
I'm drinking this tea and I'm in this beautiful pastor with these cows nearby and
Or in growing and I'm like wow. This is really cool
You're sensitive to that magical
Magical herbs of the earth. Hey Joe. You don't have to be on camera. Joe. Come on. I don't care if you're nude
I want to see your ginger bush
Uh-oh, whoa, I know they're gonna let you do you think they're gonna let him show that on YouTube psyche
You can show a backstage, but you know
I do a song about a bush and I want to play it for you real quick. Can you hear a song about a bush real quick?
Okay, you can get by with it. Let's go
Way down past the driveway gate
there's a shrub that's reached a giant state started as a hedge about four feet tall now it
blocks the sun and swallows all branches tangled thick as rope no one can see the garden
no birds moved in and formed a bush needs a trim and needs a quick but every rose inside comes out
Oh my god, this is only your act.
You're not supposed to be beating around the bush.
Yeah, oh, hey, hey psyche psyche guess guess somebody a friend of mine. I just show me a screenshot that
crazy
Yeah, it reminds me a mouth hole
Well, it does beat as well. Yeah, I mean you can never who say you the screenshot
Yeah, okay. Let me finish the Brandon went to L to
Alex is saying that I told them that I want him to
Unalive crystalline. Where's the proof?
It was he was
Yeah, he's crazy
To me so I don't know I think she's posting again against you and me like I mean, I'm not involved with him
I'm done with him. He's a psychopath and I'm glad I got the screen shot because I'm gonna
I'm gonna go ahead and contact the police about
Shit this real quick. This is my song about good
Trolls on YouTube and then I'll be right back
I'll drink a couple beers with your couple cigarettes, but you got to know you're here at Joe's hangout
Joe so I don't know where the real Joe is, but I like to meet him
We got a ginger in the chat
I'm not worried about it. She's a cool guy
Right in my pillow case nigga. I got the weed right here. Oh my god. Look at that
Look at that. I was gonna ask where's your blunt
Actually
This guy's a drug dealer
I may be able to talk to my voice psyche, not like no other people.
Okay, but first of all, when you say hi to oceans, and when you say hi, you can't.
No, I may not. No, I may not.
Yes, you may. Right now, or I'm going to say...
Yes, you may.
Bye, ocean, wherever you are.
Yeah, that's why I don't trust him. He doesn't even know me. He just goes by whatever
Yeah, yeah, cuz you're it's a lie Joe open your eyes, okay
Joe I would say by the ocean
Sad to Karen Joe, I heard you
I heard the traffic lights
tomorrow. Get in. Come on.
The traffic lights may turn
tomorrow. It's down on my bed.
That's a good chicken face
impression. That's uh that's
Jimi Hendrix. Hey, well, the
Go ahead.
What was your question?
Someone's leopard print.
Jimi Hendrix.
Is he trying to hypnotize me?
Hey, Joe.
What's it like being an angry red-headed person that's what I want to find out
I don't think I'm angry, I'm not having a good time
I am red-headed, but I don't think I'm angry
But he's not an angry
I wouldn't join him, I wouldn't have a good time
I wouldn't join him, I wouldn't join him, I wouldn't join him
Yes. Oh, my God, guys, there was a video of Joe and I kissing and it might have been an AI video.
I don't know what the fuck is there really a race at all. The internet. No, no.
Who made it? I think it was Tripp think I think made it and he made Joe. Joe is French kissing me in the video
And it's I watched I bet you watch it every day and jerk all to the top. So I drink off to it every day
It's the best no, no, I really
Guess his name is Carl. We were Carl
I know besides me. I really did join someone to smoke. We would you drink a beer with you? I'll be quiet
I'll turn my camera off. I want to smoke
Enjoy, I think Carl wants to join in the party. Okay
The psyche psyche listen to me. I don't know why Alexander is bringing me into this whole mess
I have nothing to do with that. Okay. Well, what if it's longer about that?
i'm not i'm not talking to you joe please joe please joe please be quiet okay so i didn't
either what you didn't meet me why does Mimi contact me on instagram oh i'm telling me the
tour about carl is that right there that's that's completely different from what
nozandra's been doing lately what but she called me a pdf so i'm going to go into you lately
i know i heard and she called me a pdf too that's what i'm saying why she pulled me into this you know
i think we live on planet pdf i think everyone must know and when i when i joined uh crystal
anz right i joined crystal anz uh panel right to troll her and it worked you know um so of course
alexander is always watching she's probably watching right now so now i gotta get pulled into
I'm not involved with that Carl. No, I'm just saying I'm just saying I don't know
We're almost in bed together
Listen listen Joe chill out, okay chill, please I just don't know what's going on because I'm not in this like I used to okay
There's none of it makes any sense.
I mean, you have to, you have to basically, you know,
twist around your brain with the screwdriver
to understand what's going on in this world.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, it makes no sense.
Here's what we have, here's what we have here.
We have, I and X is a good-hearted person.
We have Oceans is a good-hearted person.
Joe, he has the best blow job this side of town.
Oh gosh, you please stop, dude.
Listen, listen, the way, the way I seen,
I seen, I seen a little bit.
of what Alexandra did that that live on me, right? Like hyper focus on me. I knew what she was doing.
She was trying to replay DX to come after me. I know Karen, I next, you know, Dan, what was she's doing?
She's trying to get the jet to turn on me and come after me and like come on
I'm gonna do my DX there's nobody cares right now
I'm a reader too. I can do my own reasons. Thank you
Oh, you didn't reading you do I got it. Okay. Um, I next I've been to read is um, well
I started to read over 10 years going on YouTube for free by the way. Yeah. Oh
Read yourself like you can't be a car. No, actually, I actually Joe actually I do I haven't done in a long time
But yeah, I can do
Yeah, stop stop. I'm not here for that. I'm not here for this. Yeah, and then you have salt and pepper pubic here
It's okay. I don't care how old you are
Ashley, it's not like that down there, but I'm just saying dark is it darker than beat his bush? So oh my gosh, Karen
You hear him Karen?
I'm not saying that he's saying that
Oh, I'm so sorry. I'm not saying that don't go there
I don't mean it beat his bush. He wants to go there though. See that
He was like he chill out psyche chill out dude. I'm here. Just I'm here just to address that
I don't know what's going on because I'm running this pool like
I'm part of what's going on Alexander has put me in this like I'm against her like everyone else. I'm like
I don't know what's going on because I joined I
Join I joined Sam as better to expose plums you right okay cool, and then I jumped on
Chris Anne's to tour her and then after that it just went on to shit for me
I'm not saying for anyone else here, but for me, but why she bring me into this whole thing with
Alexander versus psyche Alexander versus I next Alexander versus
Brandy, yeah, I mean where do I come in is I mean I don't understand. Yeah
Well, Alice is the best the beat is the best
Inx, you know, I'm not I'm not around like that, you know, I'm not like yeah
I'm not going back and forth. I'm not doing that tipper
Alexander is a best friend to me. I'm just saying I'm not playing victim
I'm just saying that come back. I'm like, what I don't understand what's going on. That's all
I think she's just very sensitive, you know, and when you're that sensitive
She's very loose with Japan's Sam's ancestry, that's all I was saying
Ow! Psyche!
Psyche, why do you, why do you sound like you're talking over like a like a
Like a radio or whatever
What are you talking over nigga? You don't hear your voice your voice is like for you
Fucking right here. Oh, I don't know what's going on
Something about me. It's actually a cool effect. I mean, but I'm just saying oh my god. I'll kill you in real life, but
Chill out Joe chill out. You're sounding like that Brandon guy
Your ass will be rolling around in a wheelchair when I get done with you
Right and then what happened when Hector when you went out there remember you're hiding right, right?
I'm still hiding right
Hector Hector drove across the nation California all the way to Maryland
And you were nowhere to be found shot. He was already in Maryland retard. No, he drove out there
Okay, he drove from California. He drove
Yeah, he's from Raquel. Yeah, he's in Raquel. Yeah. Yeah
How's it feel to be the smartest man
How's it buddy?
It feels good to know everything. I see how's it feel about breakers back in it?
Gosh, that's good
You really want you want to do it to me or the panel, but yet this guy trained me up with you in real life and you were hiding
Right, I've been trained. Trust me. I know trust me. I know karate if I wanted to if I wanted
You know, oh, you know, wait, well, you know karate. What kind of what kind of cruddy the cruddy kick that sir
You I want to kick wait, wait. Just just karate like this karate that that's spelled C. R. O. D. D. Y. It's pronounced karate
Yeah, right, right. Well, I know American Kimpo. That's a former karate. I did too, but Carl, I
Kimpo when I was 16. Good for you. Good for you. Yeah. Good for you. Good for you. Did you get your black belt?
Didn't go that's that then we moved
But you still remember that stuff. There's like yes, yes
Especially the way how you can put your hand the bottom part of your palm against your nose and that'll break their nose
It does it goes into your brain
American Kimpo doesn't American Kimpo is not fucking around. They'll show you
They'll teach you shit.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
Yep.
That's my family right there, you know?
Well, American Kempo.
Yeah, righty.
Really?
Yeah, it's Kempo.
I've never heard that before.
So you said it.
Only remember taking five stories.
There you go.
I got to the yellow belt, and then we moved.
That's good though, that's still good though.
Yeah, it's exposed to dogs who get to know them.
That's the problem.
That's so good.
I don't want to say Karen, but that's still good though.
That's still good.
And yeah, INX, I got to be with you.
I just heard some stuff.
I'm like, I don't know what's going on.
I mean, I'm not in this.
No, me either.
Because now that weirdo, Brandon is coming at me lying
and let's improve when he's dangerous.
Well, you see what that?
I can't keep up because I heard like two days ago,
You better a cool one that now you're not I mean it's going back and forth because he started Brent. Yeah, he went nuts
I didn't know he was crazy like that. I remember Alex
Listen, Brenda's not crazy. He's not crazy. I'm just saying. I don't know what's going on. I can't keep up
I'm not in this. I'm out
He just goes yeah, but I've seen him go nuts. So Carl
He goes I understand. I understand. I understand. But I mean, I'm just saying that
but two days ago both you're fine and now like you're not see i'm out of the loop i'm out of the
loop not at all but but he started threatening me now go ahead and expose all of that and now he's
lying and i told him go kill are you sure he wasn't just throwing you though maybe maybe he just
Please don't say you've got mental issues when you're done. I'm playing devil's advocate here. I'm playing devil's advocate
I don't know. I wasn't there. I didn't see it. I'm just saying. Yeah, I don't know
But if I have to I'll play the video that Gamble sent me because see he was going nuts on
Okay, okay, so when I joined Chris and I was trying her about Gamble being my my managing mod
She's so so she's so fucking stupid, you know
She took it like literally, you know, because I know she's getting butter because she's low-key DX
I was trolling her but she took it literally and all that stuff and she's so stupid
anyways
Well, it's a lot of BS at least it's not real life. So we shouldn't care. It's not real life. Of course not. Of course not.
Yeah, but her rubber babies are real though. Her rubber babies are real, right?
Those silicone babies, that's weird. She had like a nursery. Remember back in the days that she remember she wanted rooms like a bunch of crypts, like a nursery she had.
That's weird. Yeah. She had a nursery for them. Yeah. And she was showing them. Yes. They're
expensive though. She had a nursery. She had a nursery of them. Like Kepper's patch. She had
a couple of patched kids. And he just like head turned around in a circle like my mind. Like,
oh my god. That's like possession. That's like a that's like a scary movie.
I was thinking, that's like a scary movie I've seen.
Yeah, Joe stopped it, stop.
Joe, you may be onto something, please stop.
But yeah, I'm caring, I just remember that.
I remember that, that she had a nursery.
She was showing it this back in the day.
We're back in the days back, though.
So, I guess.
Christina was saying that oh because of beta that's why I found her channel. No, I knew about you back in IP two days
When you were joining the panel, I'm sorry when you were joining the RV with captain on 10, you know
Um, I don't know about you from from be there. I knew I knew about you before be there
And they kicked her off. He get he kicked her off. So she I saw her. Did you see did you see the stream?
Did you see the same stream that I saw that when she was been drinking and she got on that scooter?
She fell in her face remember she crashed that was hilarious
Yeah, I saw a clip. Yeah, that was nice all live. It was hilarious. I said
No, no, well, I mean
I was there playing the background. I saw that I thought was hilarious. Please get up and crash again. Yeah, I remember that
And she was crying a ship. It's dramatic crying. You know like a drape like face playing into the concrete
Of course, she's crying. She's a woman. Well, it's actually on that. Actually on the street on asphalt. Yeah
I thought that was the best thing ever best thing I've ever seen
I didn't see her though. She could have gotten really
I want to see her do that again and also to I never saw but there's a clip of Alexandra on the scooter
Same kind of scooter falling. I wish I seen that live
Let me I saw the clip. I thought it was fantastic. Fall again. Please fall again. Yeah. Oh my goodness
They're not getting hurt Joe. They're just getting banged up. Come on, dude. What the hell is that a picture?
It's more of a listen. It's more of a bridge to the ego than he is like literally like physically. Okay. Come on
I didn't tell me what that is, please. I don't know what that is. Who is that? Thank you. Oh
Oh my gosh, I'm gonna get nightmares. Look at this old hag right here
That's really her that's just no that's a I that's a no no no that that's Christine right there. That's Christine. Oh my gosh
It's not how did you get that psyche? Where'd you get that picture psyche? You're gonna give me nightmares, please stop
Yeah, that's me
No, it's not you know that she was your fucking mother fuck her steam fuck her
That's the better picture. Yeah, that's right there. Yep. That's right there. Mm-hmm. I need a glass of milk
So my story
Is he snoring again?
No, that's my little dog snoring.
Oh, okay.
Well, I have two little dogs.
One of them, my little girl snores, right?
The little one, female, but my little boy,
he doesn't snore at all.
Oh, really?
That is not Christy.
Hey, INX, I guess that some people say
I live in your room,
but I'm in a house, though.
I streamed always from his back room, but now I live in a room, really?
Who said you were in a room?
Is this an idiot or not?
Yeah, don't say anything.
Some of the moths from Sandman, I've literally walked around this house,
but they still say that I live in a room.
I don't rent a room fucker. I'm in a house. Okay. I have this house to myself. What the fuck out of here?
I believe you. Why are you yelling at us? We believe you. Why are you yelling at me and I'm sorry? I don't know
I'm not allowed
Yeah, because it sucks that people make up shit like that. It's
Joe you don't know I've done shit in the world and I don't do that shit anymore. I'm off
Well, I know the thing is that the ones they say that are in chat
They'll never join the panel and say that see I'm like, it's a weak try
They're trolls and they'll never come up. They'll never come up. Yeah
Well, they're not figures. I don't do that. I'm live on FaceTime. Yeah, I next I don't expect I don't expect you to come up
I mean, we all know what you look like, you know what I look like
Let me say but these other ones don't make come on really like like I stop just chill out
You know, and you probably you probably don't I didn't have my real picture on my profile even that's his name
It gave me comments and then they're blowing
Let me ask you a question
Next let me ask you a question
Like maybe two or three months ago. I was born in 1960 dumb ass. You're older than
And and I look younger because because I get hit on by younger guys and even my
There you go. Hell yeah
Question so a few months ago clumsy had messaged me on Instagram goes. Hey, I next is looking looking for you
So he gave you my my Instagram, but you never did contact me though. I didn't find you. I thought you probably had me blocked or something. So no, I don't know. I don't have a blog. I don't have a blog. It's always Grand Illusion on Instagram. I'll give you mine. I'll give you mine. It's private. So I don't take other people unless they have permission to follow me. But it's well, you can find me. You can find me on Instagram is Grand Illusion, you know.
Clumsy said he gave it to you
No, it didn't work. I clicked on it and it looked like I was blocked but I don't block anyone
Okay, so I can send you mine cuz he follows me on IG. Okay. He can give it to you
I'm saying though. What why were you trying to contact me a few months ago?
Yeah
Yeah, it was just something back then that you were gonna go live then. Yeah
Well, even back then I mean I wasn't streaming I haven't streamed since uh my last stream was last
December. I don't stream anymore in this community. You don't you don't stream anymore. Where do you
stream? I don't stream anywhere. I don't stream anywhere. No. No. Yeah, I wouldn't do it around
YouTube. There's too many trolls and too much bullshit and you know it's like I mean I may hop on
Me hop on a panel here and there about me. I don't stream anymore. You know here. Yeah
Area, okay, it's not just we all know I next this is a big it's like over
YouTube is enormous. I mean, I don't ship anywhere on YouTube though. I'm saying yeah, I just mm-hmm
I'm over that sometimes it's a bad idea because there's trolls and you go on there and it's just well, I mean
You take you take it, you know, you take a bunches as they come, you know, you know how it is I next I mean
You're gonna stream you're gonna have people support you. You're gonna have some haters there. So, you know
Whatever, I mean, I didn't I didn't stop because of that. I just like, you know, I just whatever it's not that serious to me
That's what I'm asking you about
That's why I joined you
What was going on and I'm out the loop. I'm not
So I just I know what's going on
Yeah, I don't either now. It's all of a sudden. That person is coming at
Joe can we share your your blunt
Oh my gosh, you gave me nightmares psyche. Please stop
Yeah, that's mean come on. That's it. Thank you. Please stop you give me nightmares
Please stop. I did see one
Hey, I next did you see one one brandy Q and his homeboy? They're they're at outside of
Plumsies area
No, that's what clump clumsy went. I saw the clip of his area
Yeah, he was at his own place
I just saw a clip I didn't see Brandon
Like a life, but I saw a clip on McHale. Yeah fucking press that guy fuck
Yeah, because because you didn't know what I annex I don't know why they did it I annex you didn't see what clumsy did to me
No, what did he do? Okay? Well, so I
Joined his panel a few weeks ago, right?
And I was coin clumsy offer being a gossip girl, right? So he's always he's always hitting on salmon, right for this and that, right?
But oh send this now, but he was doing the same thing that salmon does, right?
He's always in the DMs being a gossip girl with all the ladies, right? That's that's clumsy, right?
All right next, please please pay attention
Yeah, so I joined his panel right to call me out on just on that right I joined his panel calm collective like I am now
And when I joined, he was like, oh, look at this guy.
He was really getting emotional when I joined.
You know what he said?
I want to talk about fucking kids.
I want to rape this man and he kicked me.
Oh my God.
What?
I was like, and he kicked me.
I'm like, what the?
I had nothing to say.
I mean, he kicked me.
Okay, I just left.
So guess what though?
Guess what?
Joe, listen.
So INX, listen.
So after that, right?
I was memory. He's he's in New Mexico. I'm in SoCal, right? So he's an hour ahead of me
This guy messes me on instagram, right?
And he says that i'm going to come up to uh cal california and smash her as pussy
That's what he said. I screenshot right there, right? And then he tried to call me. He tried to call me
I scram. We've never called each other on instagram ever and then I screenshot that so when I joined his panel from my phone, right?
I tried to show him show everybody that but he's like oh, I never sent you that message your line
He was gaslighting me, but I couldn't show it because it was on my phone
I joined the panel on my phone, so guess what I went to Tommy James
I was talking about him that same day after that my annex
That same day because I joined Tommy James
Penal like early in the morning that same day. I started getting these calls on my burner number that I gave him
I have a burner number, right?
I gave him that burner number last year, by the way.
He started to call me and he was saying all this stuff, right?
I got the text messages and I got the voicemail from him, right?
But I didn't check it till two weeks later.
I opened it up on IAX and you can hear him whispering.
He's saying he's going to rape me.
He's going to rape me.
I mean, his friend's going to rape me.
So I exposed him for that, yeah.
I expose him for that. Yeah, that's weird. Are you sure? Yeah, that's sure. I got I got the I got the receipts
I got the proof. Yeah, you can hear the cadence in his voice
Everybody knows I did it on Sam ends right to expose him because I don't want that content
I mean, I don't see me no more, right? Yeah, I did it on Sam ends and everybody agreed. I don't need I can validate myself
I know what I heard. Okay. It was definitely clumsy whispering, but they all heard it and they said that was definitely clumsy, too
That's weird
behind the scenes.
Come on, see?
That's weird, dude.
You're a weirdo.
And then after that, he says, oh, you want to run to Salmon and cry?
And then he goes, then he says, I'm an old, lonely, coquette.
I've never done coke in my life.
But now I'm old, I'm drunk, I'm a coquette.
Well, guess what?
Last year, he used to draw my pen on.
He never says I'm a coquette.
He never said I was old or drunk.
I'm a kid out of here, dude.
Just chill out.
Well, he never is.
He never is.
He's just doing too much, you know, no, that's between him and I right? I'm not I'm not I'm not hate bonding with anyone
That's just him and I right. Yeah, I didn't know he was gonna come sideways like that with me
All I was gonna do was call him out to be a gossip girl behind the scenes
Uh, he was doing with beta. He did with Mimi and other ones. That's all I was going to call him out for
He brought the weird stuff. He brought up kids. He brought up kids. That was weird
And then he started to send those messages and voice mails behind the scene like get out of here. That's weird
Really? He was sending you voice mails. You can keep I told you I you want me to play right now
I can play right now. Well, I go ahead flight one play one. That's here. I
Play right now
Are you next? Really? Yeah, okay. Okay. I don't know what happened for you today. You have total permission. I'm gonna play it right now.
I got it right here. Play it right now. Let me pull it up. Are you next? Hold on. Hold on. Let me put it up right now.
Or we are holding on. We are, um... Joe wants to hear it.
Hold on. I just think it's funny. Okay. Okay. You ready? Okay. I'm gonna play it. Okay. I gotta put the phone down
Okay, so you can hear that I'm playing for my tablet. Okay
So let me turn the volume real quick. Okay
Now this this is clumsy leaving a voicemail to me. Okay, here we go
Hold up. Listen
Oh my god, hold on hold on one more time
Joe Joe Joe shut up one more time one more time I'm gonna play it again Joe shut up
Hold on Joe stop I'm gonna play it again. This is so horrible Joe you hear that whispering that that's coming
Yeah
And he denied that too. Yeah
It sounds like him, but what was he saying? I couldn't understand he says he says that him
Him and his friends are gonna fuck me my ass like I fucked my nephew. That's disgusting. Oh
My god, can you play it again?
No, that's okay, that's okay
I can play the game, but Joe is killing his fucking this pen right now. Joe
You got it Joe, please Joe, please be quiet. Okay, please. It's not your battle either. So you don't tell me
There you go. See I can't
Joe sounds for Thursday, I'll suck your dick. Just let him play with it. Oh faggot
Okay, I'll be there for 30 seconds at least quick quick girl and the thing is that okay. I'm gonna play it again. Okay
Okay, ready, I'm playing again. Yeah, this was this was on this was on June 7th. Okay, hold on here we go
Listen
Sounded like a kid
That's clumsy whispering
What's Closie Whisperer? Is that like a little evil kid for that movie?
Here, okay.
The thing I'm saying is that we're talking.
That we're talking.
Hello, Mrs. Catacos.
Psyche. Psyche. Psyche, listen to me.
If I send you or IA Next to ask you like audio clip,
you can hear it on your buzzer, headphones, whatever.
You can hear it better than.
No, man.
You're a la-la-li-oxin-free.
I'm just saying.
I'm chunky now.
That was that chunk of your clumsy this guy. This guy went this guy went sideways on me. I'm like, what the fuck?
I mean, this was on my burner number. He was calling it. He was calling it on the answer
I didn't even show you the messages. He sent me on this burning number at the text message
I never replied
Were they sick?
Yeah, yeah, I know I know I don't even I can't even I don't even want to hear but do you know
Inax
Inax myself and brandon q
There's a there's a shocking clip I have to play you. It's only a few minutes long
This is a shocking clip of accusations made against I and this better shock me it better be shocked
Yeah, he's crazy
Wait till you say the my text
I mean the other day and I gave him one last chance. He apologized and he does the same thing. He goes nuts
Oh my gosh, I don't even want that played psyche. I want to be done with him
There's not much to say so I'm just going to present them but basically earlier this evening
the individual known as Brandon Q92, the individual known as Psyche, and the individual known as INX publicly stated that they want to assault, as in sexually assault.
someone who is loosely affiliated with the Juggalo community.
I wouldn't lie, all because I blogged to her YouTube request.
So let's just take a look.
Yeah, right. Yeah, right, sure.
I was like, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was, I was,
I like twisted bro. I don't even like ice skating anymore. I like twisted bro and fucking
That ass is good though.
God, son.
Sorry.
I made a mistake.
These alternate reality pictures are a little bit too much, I think.
No, I want, if Tommy James lived, I would have thought Tommy James every...
Not all of them will.
Oh my goodness.
I was worried.
I'm sorry.
Literally, I'll say Tommy James.
I mean, as I raise my foot in his ass, go ask Tommy James then.
and
Yeah, he keeps talking about a red ball and sends me a few pictures of Gamble with a red ball.
Is that the White Sea Virgo?
I think it looks like the White Sea Virgo.
Did I do this?
That's the Virgo.
That's White Sea Virgo.
Apparently they were reviewing one of my copywritten songs and videos.
And for some reason, these sickos were compelled to say that they wanted to sexually assault Tommy James.
All right, where's proof?
Where's the proof?
He just makes up all kinds of shit.
Watch your back, Tommy.
Watch your back.
Just because he let her down.
He didn't want normal people down.
She's right.
Alex is right.
Normal people don't know about the sexual assault.
Joe, that's bullshit, Joe.
There's no proof.
You need to look at proof.
I believe you've got the proof, Jim.
I thought it works in the same place.
had me cross paths with some of these demonic monsters by seeing what was wanting me to come
on her channel she gets that second the first time she invited me to Olive Garden and that
Melissa came and gave me the message. I was wondering how about a little bit of a nice
You just not a real retelling rest. Yeah, you're right. They have
been ones up here like Milano. I like all garden though. I love
all garden. I do too. I'd like it. I like it. Red is the best
right that bread they have. Hey, what is this? Yes. What the
fuck is that? I've never met Zaya in my life. But look, I go
comfortable with him already. She made a long turn five.
Yeah, it's like a horror movie like every one of these things is it's scarier and scarier like
Look at how bald I am Carl look at my she made my hair like this. I know I know I know
Hey everyone, but the way though, but yes
Look at my hair
I know I know I know I know nice
Yesterday they said I live in a section eight apartment. I'm in a fucking full-size house fuckers. Look it around. Look around
Oh, hey mom. Hey mom. Hey mom. Hey dad. Come on like really like get out of here
Hey, mom. Hey dad, you know like hey mom. Hey dad
Well, I'm gonna put them right
I'm gonna perm right let me go in the backyard. Let me show you the pool, but I mean it's actually
I've been in a fucking full-size house right now like
What do you say
If I can't swim in your pool one day, but I'm gonna wear the American flag speedo
No, no
Okay, that reminds me let me ask you a question psyche
You you taught Alexander that I threatened I was going to live you listen. I have never trained you at all
I never said that I put that on my dead parents. I never said that to you.
Look at my eyes. See my eyes. I've never said that to you.
I don't own any guns. I don't own any guns. I will never throw anybody like that.
Please don't please don't say that on my name. Okay. I would never do anyone like that. I'm sorry. Yeah.
Look at this guy.
This is how he kisses.
Oh my gosh.
That's how he makes it better, huh?
How are you next?
Wow
I
I used to I used to do that stuff. I used to I used to I used to you can't shake the magic car. It's always coming
I used to I used to do that step. I don't do it anymore
That's right, you were the silver fox
This is textbook narcissism
And she'll fucking drop you and she'll break you down, you know
Yep. Yep. There's a pattern. There's a pattern with her.
She did the same thing with other streamers too. She's a pattern with her.
I know I've researched this so deeply. I mean,
I have videos analyzing all the psychology of this. I mean,
exactly. I mean, I, even the AI sees it. I mean,
AI says and fluttering things about me too. It says I'm kind of real cool leader,
which I'm not, but it does kind of pin it down. Like, well,
at the end of the day,
like I'll show you like I just want to show you this real quick this is like a five-minute thing
because she is like oh gosh oh it's only five minutes more A.I. stuff five minutes five minutes
it's five minutes okay five minutes by the way Carl my next click here please
sit down click here and close your eyes i'm gonna say that from now on
are you next click here please
Today we're stepping right into strange, vapor-weather-soaked, late-night world of
the live stream listed on a channel called Psyche's Nightmares.
We're going to clinically analyze how we evolve our immune system and we'll be unfolded
there in real time.
What starts as a quiet, well-informed college broadcast quickly devolves into an intense
study of human behavior, power dynamics, and digital confrontations.
What actually happens when profound isolation meets a live audience?
My loneliness is killing me. That raw unfiltered admission of emotion spoken by a user named Alexandra
Midway through the stream is literally the engine driving the entire
Like a lightning rod and as you'll see
Hey, Carl, if you're just buzzing in my mouth, I would be yelling at you right now.
What? What did you say to me?
Nothing.
Oh my gosh look at him my next look at him.
Look at him.
He's going, I'm cute.
Oceans is real quiet now.
Yeah, oceans is just watching.
He's trying to convert me.
All right, next.
I don't know.
Look at this guy.
I'm cute, Carl. I'm looking better than I used to do, too.
Aren't I better?
They used to say I'm like...
How would it go that far?
What?
I wouldn't say you're like that.
Is it always time for me to die from it?
I don't judge you either way, you know, before or after.
Hey, just tell me I'm cute, please.
Or I'm going to kick you off the show.
Say it, say it, Carl.
I'm not going to answer that.
Okay, okay. I like how you guys play hard to get.
Oh my god, I see I next you think oh, he's gonna look at this
No, I next is instigating I next stop stop it
He's already doing it
Oh
Okay, because this is even scarier than that, okay
He has his father's eyes
What the crap is this
It's a Rosemary's baby, a Rosemary's baby, an old baby.
Oh my God, oh, it's sad.
He came up from hell and begat a son of mortal woman.
Hail, Scythe!
Satan is his father, and his name is Adrian.
He shall overthrow the mighty and lay waste their temples.
He shall redeem the despised and wreak vengeance
in the name of the burned and the tortured.
Hail, Adrian!
Hail!
I want to I want to address really Nancy in chat. Hey Nancy I thought you were gonna do that live
Oh my god, psyche psyche, can I please stop please?
Hey, thank you. Hi, sweetheart. How are you today?
Um, I actually wanted to tell you that you were right Mexico on your
Yeah, you have mystical powers for sure.
Thank you.
I thought I might have some power.
Hey, if you know who Musically As Marty was,
he was asking for sports bets.
I don't know much about sports, but tell me
the color of the football team's pants.
And I'll go look at their butts, and I'll make a prediction.
And I think they had white shorts on.
They had white shorts.
Did I predict that too?
I'm not sure, but if you hate either like $5
Jockstrap and
Hey Carl, do you have a jockstrap? I just want to know you are Mexico
Mexico
Mexico, well Karen is Brazilian
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yeah, I can tell. I can tell. I can tell. They call them Chilangos. They're from Mexico City.
No. Have you traced back my last time? It goes back to the Morse. I know my ancestors were black,
but we're going way back though. Yeah. Wow. Yeah.
But my mom's side, she's European and Irish.
We thought she was Mexican.
She was race Mexican and my dad Mexican, but more Spanish, I guess it got a weird, you
know.
I'm just.
It does.
Let me say one thing.
I had like three friends that all like paid money to go to ancestry comm and I swear my friend Scott
He was like I'm related to the guy to kill Lincoln and my other friend was like I'm related to King Henry the third
Yeah, yeah, that's a way
Joe please meet yourself, please
Reality Nancy says she may go live exposing you and also Christine. Excuse me exposed me for what though?
Really nancy
I have a question for you. Do you know
I have a certain I have a certain woman. I want to ask you a question about do you know this woman right here?
I'm sorry. That was a difference
Okay, hold on. Yeah, I
Yeah, I
Do you know this man? Do you know this man? Have you heard of Minnie Manson?
No
Okay, have you heard of this man? Oh, no the scammer in the community
That's a real person
He's doing AI stuff. He's doing AI stuff.
Oh man, that's made me put a beard on her.
I don't know who that is.
That is not Alexandra right there.
Come on.
No, but he put, yeah, that's not her.
Don't do that.
Yeah, no, that's going too far.
I'm sorry, I know it's going too far.
Okay, okay.
This is me.
I'm sorry.
Okay, so we are just answers so she was gonna say she was gonna expose Brian. Yeah, see I wouldn't be there
I want to listen to it. I want to see here. You're gonna say, but
Yeah, yeah, no, she said I may go like exposing she meant that's that was my question to her
Carl not Carl. No, she's been beat it in clumsy. So do Mexicans love Harry buttholes
Oh, they do.
I thought you said this guy.
This guy.
They have butt holes.
Oh, my gosh.
Stop, dude.
Stop.
In Venezuela, you know, they're doing too much, dude.
The men put stockies until they can find a way.
All right, next.
He's doing too much.
He needs to sit all down.
Yeah, no, man, that's the Venezuela.
She's just saying me and peps and someone's doing no.
I didn't see that means that's what that's what I saw that.
Yeah. What is this?
What are you showing?
Who is in the background?
Is that peps?
Oh, poor peppy.
Yeah, that's peps peps.
So what about Joe?
Dude
Like you know what you're doing you're like Sam and showing all these clips and stuff we're showing these pictures
You're like Sam and and stop yeah, who is
That was
Yeah, is that a real person a sweet? Yes? Yes? Yes? Please please?
You know what really nasty I should go live I should expose those ones too. Yeah
Yeah, you should you should go live
that's what he looks like now like no I saw that disgusting it was disgusting
yep I saw that that's that's what he looks like it's so sad it's so sad no
you're right I should I mean I don't go live anymore but I mean I should I mean
Listen, I know I messed up. I said some horrible stuff about Mimi and her daughters. I mean, I know I'm to that hundred percent, right?
You guys like tequila?
Yes, but these other ones they got to be exposed.
I can't drink it straight. There's no way
Tequila is it's called tequila
Well, so that's yeah, well, I know tequila, but there's tequila. Yeah. Tequila. I know tequila too.
It's going to kill you. Drink all of it. It's going to make you feel like. Oh, to kill you. You're
right. Yeah. Yeah. Because you're not used to it or the one you drink the next day. When it's
when it's mixed in drinks, I can do it without doing shots. No way. It's like. Because the next
Yeah, you're gonna have a killer hangover. No wonder it doesn't let me drink
Fuck if I had 1800 I would take a shot. I don't have 800 right now. Yeah, I like that window
I like I said, they're on me right now. Okay. Okay. Let's take a shot. Let's take a shot right now
Let's go one two three. Let's go
Joe taking a shot to or I don't drink that ball. I don't Jill is so
Drinking beer, I don't drink a beer. I'll drink a beer. You guys drink yourself
You fucking Ricky
My next
Yeah, do you remember you remember that song back in the days of Margaritaville by Jimmy Buffett?
Back in my earlier years
this is very rude you're killing your panel right now
oh my gosh for a second you're killing your panel
You don't know how to run a panel psyche. Please. Please bosses
You know what you turn it when you just put this shit on like that. It's
I'm not bitchy
Okay, anyways, I next now back when I was 21 many moons ago
We were in Upland, California, right?
And after we went to a club down the street,
we went to Mark Rederville.
I'm like, what is this?
Karen, I'm sorry, I can't say that.
INX, there was like a big, there was a huge bar, right?
It was called Mark Rederville.
We went in there, of course, was on the plane.
Where's the new buffet? I mean, I always love that song. Oh, basically, we're on there just getting drunk
But the whole song the whole time they're playing that same song over again. I didn't know he had a franchise now
He had a franchise of these bars all around
Yeah, mm-hmm. It's called literally mark greaterville. That's what it was called
It's a beautiful song, yeah
Yeah, we love that song. That's why we drove all the way to Texas
And you was cool about that song though. I next was cool about that song
You can be completely completely sober and appreciate this song or you can please smash out your fucking mind drunk and you appreciate it
Yeah, I know yeah, and we were sober we were sober and I will smash up my mind and I was smashed
I was so drunk yeah, okay, okay
How many drinks before I can give you a blow job?
What?
Oh my God.
I'm not clipping.
No.
I'm clipping.
You better have a good memory because I do.
I do.
Okay.
Yeah.
You know that I'm not engaging.
He's the one who's doing it, not me.
I know.
Okay, yeah, look at this guy. Oh my god
Give me a bonus like he stopped nobody cares about this stuff right now
Correct, I'm gonna come off
Kept right. Oh my god. He's dancing. I'm literally going blind right now. Yeah
Jesus, who are they?
I think he is I do I think he is
Alright next, what do you think? You think I should go live and expose you to people or what?
I don't know, that's up to you. I mean, you know.
I'll say yeah.
Well, I mean, I'm looking at Raleigh Nancy in chat. She always exposes ones, you know.
I support her on that completely.
I mean, now we gotta watch Raleigh Nancy.
Have you ever do it?
I don't have her channel.
Raleigh Nancy, have you actually do that? I'll be there to support you. Really.
Yeah, I want to watch I want to watch I don't know her channel though
What is fall they handle the handles right there can somebody can somebody post her channel on the in the chat
Well, I next just
Happen
Nancy I'm on the phone on here. So it drops me. So I have my
Hey, really Nancy, I got a proposition for you how about if you want to expose them you can do a mindset about that
I don't I'm not there for
To create a big channel. I'm not trying to do all that, but because I'll put in my my two cents, too
How about that? Let me miss you
If you enjoy that we can collab I guess
If you want, you know, so you're gonna do it on her channel or your channel. I'm just I'm giving her a position
If she wants to do it, she can do it on my channel because I put my two cents in too about those pretty good ones.
Yeah. Can you put your channel in the chat?
I sure can yes, yes, and but if she wants to do a separate cool. I'll be there to support her
She wants to come over to my channel and do it well
We can do it really Nancy and I can put my two cents into so have you went to it? I'm not trying to create a channel
I don't care about fucking views on that shit
Yeah, I want to see it if you can put both your channels on there, not okay, right? Yes, okay. Well, okay, okay, right?
Nancy, okay. Well, let's
Let's talk about this really Nancy. Let's talk about this because I'm not trying to take anything away from what you're going to do.
I'm just saying that I can put my two cents in two on those individuals.
So if you want, you can do your separate exposure. I'll be there to support you.
I can do mine. I'm sure you'll come over to my channel and support me.
But how? How about we do it together?
That'd be kind of bad now.
I'd never do it together, by the way.
I can go, have you, have you, have you do it?
Shamir, I can join yours.
I don't know how you're going to do it, but I mean, I'm just saying, I just, I'm just
brainstorming right now.
Just brainstorming, that's all.
but rarely nasty I mean it sometimes it takes people a while to see how certain
ones are some catch on quick other ones it takes them months or years to find out
like how certain ones are I'm not saying no names for tomorrow fucking you know
that big bird that too can you know too can't stand you know yeah she's big
No, I know I know a lot about her. Mm-hmm a lot about her I next you know I was you know
I was I was in a connection with her right you know that, right? Oh, yeah, I know a lot about her behind the scenes
Yeah, you know the cards you can Sam you
I would never say that she's a catfish, which she is.
Because, because, because, on Instagram,
what she really ever did came up for me,
she was running Filters.
Mm-hmm.
The Millio.
She was.
I've seen the real beat and she's beautiful. It's the night as long
By the way, nobody nobody's hey Bonnie
Hey
Are you kidding me? She looks way older shut up Sam and get the hell out of here. Well, what do you bring him up psyche?
He runs off when barb, I mean when Barry shows up
Hey
Your Wi-Fi is fucked up man. You gotta pay your bill. Now you're trying to go out there out when you suck it
What
No, I don't I'm done. I blocked him to watch the beginning. I came out here to talk
He threatened me the other day and I told him
Be out when he came and said he'd never do that again. And then it happened again
Done okay, don't give me the content. You're talking about you
Don't give in the car. Shut up. I'll shut up. Go go talk to
Yeah, you are you're you're a petto. No, I didn't
Show proof of that weirdo
And what did you do to KK? Look at what was her name summer called you out and had you won a lead in your life
I don't delete my house. It's all right. Shut up
Well, who's that you call me a petal? What's the INS? Don't you keep? Why did I say that somebody?
Yeah, I said it. I said who is it? Who is this?
And then you want to keep it that you want to apologize. Why are you hey bonding? I didn't apologize to you
I never apologize. Oh
That was long time ago, but I saw the real you you're you're you're
I'll shut up. Go feed your dead fish. You don't have any fish in that tank.
You run away from Barry and Tommy.
You run away from Tommy and Barry, you know?
Yeah.
You run away from the cops.
So, who's that?
My punk ass bitch your mama is old and she looked like a man. Your mama is old and I got her pictures
Okay, I got everything and your brother who's gay and he
Yeah, he is
Oh my god
Showed that he great the boy
Is salmon was excited to meet up with Christine
You was excited. Yeah
Who's this person?
Where's your reality that you went to make KK with your liar?
When you're just sitting there, no clothes on, big belly.
No, no, no.
You do that.
I'm not.
Okay, you're a grown-ass man. You can never come up. Say man imagine being a man
And you're so yourself can't come up. He's not and I can't come up anytime. I can come up anytime homeboy
Yeah, you can't go you can never you can never
Understand women
Listen be a man to come up pay for Mimi's ticket
There you go. See this is the person be a man right now be a man right now come up be a man right now come up
There you go. No, you're gonna say I'm gay
I'm gay, right? I'm gay. I'm gay. I'm gay. I'm gay because I want to see you came up, right?
Right
Mistake I've never talked with Karen ever on panel
Like you say it like you say
No, I didn't you look at you about great being kids. That's what you did playing
Listen Joe even told you get the hell out nobody
Yo, you like any of you would like to talk about great big kids, why is that?
70 who said it show proof of that dumbass you
Yes, you said it yes because you break the kid what shut up and you know
I put that on my dead parents and my dead brother. I've never done cooking my life. I like how Clumsy calls this bitch.
Clumsy, I've never done cooking my life. I put that on my dead parents and my dead brother.
No, who's that?
Jocer Pina. Jocer Pina. Jocer Pina.
Jocer Pina. Jocer Pina.
You really got a police report. Don't worry, there's no police report, asshole, because I didn't do shit.
Yeah, don't worry, people.
Dream people. Yeah, right. Well, how about you? You know, you lose every channel dumbass. Yeah, I like you ban evading, right?
I'll go our route. Oh, get a job
Get a job
I do have a job and I make a lot of money. I donate dumbass and you you don't have a job
Seven
A lot of people dumbass
You know who you know who I'm not gonna say their names. I mean, who did you donate with you had a good five dollars for
Eldo
Tell me, you know. Yeah, I'm not gonna go. I'm not gonna
Great
No, I didn't I mean you're a piece of shit
Okay, that's that
That comes here. I never lied. I never lied on the dead. Okay. This shit is crazy. Chill out. Let me chill out
I'm out of here, man. This is a good job. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. All right
Hey, Sam and you'd be nice
You're a weirdo to psych you the other where I like how psych collector all the weirdos on one panel
But okay, he's a weirdo, but you're his panel. You're a weirdo, right?
Right, right?
So it's all seconds of weirdo, but you're gonna see where out to
Get out of here, Sam. And really, you contradict yourself, dude.
He's trying to create content, right? So you can have it to play on his fucking show.
That's all. Yeah, I got something to play with.
Sorry. Whatever. Clumsy. Listen to me, homegirl. Not homeboy homegirl. Okay.
I have never done coke in my fucking life.
I put that on my dad parents and my dad brother, homeboy,
homegirl.
Now, you said that I lie on that.
You may have put stuff on your family, whatever,
or dad family.
You can lie about it.
I don't lie about that shit.
When I put the shit, I put that on my living baby nephews.
My nephew, he has kids.
I put that on my living baby nephews.
Their lives so God as listen me as my witness if I'm fucking lying strike him dead right now
I have never been cooking my fucking life. Get the fuck out of here dude. You're projecting homeboy
Chill out what that shit, okay? If you do that shit fine, but I've never done that shit in my whole fucking life
Okay, that's that
It's a weak troll. It's a very weak troll
You know how it is clumsy when people are doing coke. You know how they act
Karen knows how it acts and people act when they're all fucking coke
No, cuz I used to do coke that was one of my
Clumsy that's fucking way bro. Really? It's a weak fucking troll dude
Ten oceans or earlier call me a cokehead by the way, but yeah, you're a
Seven eight ten a.m. Streaming but I'm a coke where I'm asleep, right?
Clumsy chill out homeboy chill out, okay
It's just two suckies or is that really?
I think she Hey oceans oceans is still there. I think I don't know oceans are you on?
The last time I got high off of we was in 2001 and that was like a head change my buddy came up in his service
I see picking up from the airport. I got a head change that I was done with that shit
So from 2001, just alcohol and fucking cigarettes.
Let's fucking go.
Or my nephews, when they got my nephews during their 20s,
like, hey, hey, I'll go, hey, let's fucking get high.
I'm like, fuck that.
You know, they try to give me a high all these years.
Trying to get a higher.
Nobody with my beer son.
Can I go, Carl?
Can I go to your uncle?
Yeah.
What?
Can I go to your uncle for a short?
They come uncle. Can I call you Papi or Theo they come in
Theo that means God though. You have a car light is
Like I next be here this guy. I next be here this guy right now
That's a theology theosophy God Theo means God in Greek
Theo
No, I know what you're saying
Stop that's what it is with the word a Greek is I am next he's getting sexual right now
Yes
They get real sexual up in here. I don't know guys
My god, is that your young Carlos in 1965? Oh my god. Is that fucking Pablo Escobar, but yeah, that's 2020 right there
That's 2020 feel Castro in like 1973 or something Jesus Christ back to the fabric stop
Stop, I don't think he a lot of Castro is cute, but I would blow him for a Cuban cigar
Oh
Yeah, I hear that I'm reading the chat what they're saying about Sam. Yeah, that's mean Sam is a crooked teeth
No, he's missing teeth. All right. Is around it. Nancy's still there. No, I'm afraid
Let's do that exposure we can do on my channel. How about that? I'm not really invested in the shit, but
For that for them. Yeah, I'll expose him hell. Yeah, I would hell. Yeah, I would do it right now expose that motherfucker
I can go live right now, but why I'm not taking anything away from psyche
Do it for the 12 viewers that are up in here
I'm not going to take anything away from here right now
All right, I got you're a real man at least
Shut the fuck up, Joe.
I tell you one thing though when I go live you're not going to be on the panel. How about that?
Oh, well, that's you kill it. You kill it. You kill it. You kill it. Now when I'm done then you can join
But when the exposure the expose a you're not gonna be on it
You'll kill it dude. Like you're killing it right now. You're like a
Yeah, what is that? Why do you keep putting that picture on there is?
Who is that? Maybe likes it. Hey, uh, psyche, um, why don't you, why don't you post that, uh, the screenshot of when clumsy was outed on Facebook for being a full-time mail escort, full-time, by the way.
Okay, you are post-coral slang, so we can all-
Did you see that? Shut the fuck up, Joe. Um, I am next. Did you see that? Did you see that?
I think that saw the clip. Why play it again? Yeah, why?
Well, it's not a clip. It's a screenshot
Yeah, but I mean on here. I mean, that's kind of mean like that picture of the main by the way
Not you not you
Right now here. I'm just saying though. Do you know what community you're in and you say that's mean fuck this
This is nature of the community right now
Yeah, I didn't know that now now. Okay. Let's talk about this. No, he says that his and his defense
He says like, oh well, I was doing that to troll the community. Um, but look at the date though. That's like what 2015 to current
Oh, I didn't see that. I'd never saw any of that. Yeah. Oh, see you didn't see. Okay. Well when I when I do the exposure
I'll make sure to show it
He literally said in his old fucking picture that he was a full-time male escort
Clumsy, by the way
I know when it talks his name, but I mean you you'll see it you'll see it
He did it
I don't care about that. I don't care about anything. It does. It's just like
Listen for the record and that's this thing cool
But yet he wants to fucking project
He wants to divert from what people are saying about him
He wants to project on other people like saying they're weirdos and they're doing some weird shipping
He's doing weird shit, you know
That's my view right there and jump over your roof get on your roof right now and jump off at first
You understand me I can jump off my roof and jump in the pool. How about that?
Well, who is
Who is Wallace they said Wallace is disappointed in you salmon or Sam? Oh
George was a George was is gone those two guys there was two guys I ran though that ran account. Oh
They're my own moderators, and yes, they do they did use to moderate for me. Listen those those are old accounts
And these other ones that came up there. They're fucking their fake accounts. They're not George was their fake accounts
No, they're talking about Wallace and he's he's disappointed in salmon
Well, whoever this is fake
All right
When are you gonna go live you should go less in time
You know what Carl I think too of somebody that you know two of our ex-friends when you know
We're wanting to go live, but if I put
Because they don't know of these other people they can be
Yeah, yeah, so so they want to so I'm thinking about it so but so you don't want to you don't want to do a live
Right, you know what started last year we put that put the link there publicly you want to give it to somebody behind the scenes, right?
Maybe if I do it, I'll decide I mean I know how to go live
But it's but now I have to figure out how to do the modding and all that I haven't gone to that
You don't have to mod anyone you just go in life. What the what do you do?
No, but but I mean like to add yeah, that would be new to me. I mean you don't have to mod anyone. You're just going live
Right, you're right. Are you kidding me?
Come on.
You're making excuses. Just just just go live. You know what? I think so. I think so
It's been a while since I tried it and I hit it went live and I shut it off
I'll tell you what other channel you go live in your mommy and I'll ban everyone. I'll go rogue. I was clean fucking
I was cleaning the house
You won't see nobody in check because I'll fucking I'll sweep. I'll sweep that shit. I'll sweep it. Yeah
Yeah, so it's mostly about the barb. Oh
My gosh, that old hack they need to show their proof about
She said that she said that she said on crystal ends that she would
Do something to me if I joined a panel this old fucking hag like what?
Like you do what to me?
She said nobody trying to be somebody. Yeah, I'm saying like chill out old lady. Chill out
No, I didn't I didn't see her say I didn't I don't watch them up, you know, so I've joined a couple of times
You know
One more so I mean then we're gonna do I guess like he's probably watching it. It's very we should be watching it
Oh, actually, I guess I want to show you a little something real quick. No, I don't want to hear
What a fight all the time
He's whispering
That's clumsy. Remember, Joe, Joe, Joe got that. Got muscles. He got muscles.
Remember when Carl played that clever clumsy whisper and I think, hey, you're right, Carl.
Clumsy is a weirdo. What did you say in chat right now? What?
Saki, would you ask Carl if he considered himself a retard? Really?
Wow, it's ever a buff. Hold on. There was it. Don't look what anybody else said look what nightbot said a temporary
Bump ten plus points. Hell yeah nightbot. Thank you
He says
For you to flex again. I don't listen to the person in Chatham as that Kate rainbow Yankees. I don't do that
No, it's it's psyche that's saying that in the chat
Well, you know, and I'll just leave psyche wanted more because that's a look
Listen, I don't know anything about that. Okay. I don't know anything about that with your scene right now
I don't know what you're saying. I know I don't anything about it. All right. I don't what you're saying
You keep saying this. I don't I don't anything about that. Do you know anything about that?
You know anything about that?
Want to get closer you want the hard art this accent says and I GG or right at the end. Thank you, man
I don't give a really does yeah, you want to play? Yeah, I didn't know I don't come see
I don't know anything about that. Okay. I know what you're talking about. Let's see
We don't talk about that
All right, I annex when you're gonna go live this this week. I don't know. I gotta talk to them
Don't probably talk to you. You gotta you gotta consult with yourself and make what you should go
No, because because one of them, uh, you know, she works till late
Oh, okay, and yeah, and then her husband
Sometimes and
Well, I mean you can go live because when you decide and if she if she can join she can have nothing
program are those of the speakers and do not necessarily reflect the views or
positions of any entities they represent.
Do your discretion is advised clumsy over there talking the worst shit the worst shit about me in my in your chat
Talking about salmon dog mom all that and then you're gonna be upset is somebody if I killed a spider that had nothing to do with you
And and he's bringing up his own mom. I don't represented you. I would get it
Show it
I want to see I don't want you're talking about I want to see it.
We name it because I don't remember anyone naming it.
So I'm saying this is you.
I don't want you to tell me when you're on the fucking panel.
I'm not how you got to focus.
Be the I'm here.
Be the we got to fuck.
Yeah, I don't even know.
He has nothing to do with sight.
You know, I'm going to just not let him up.
I'm an open panel.
And I don't want to say they man.
They don't come up.
We is going to be rallied over some fucking talking about weird shit.
We're having to talk once again.
You know, it's better that everyone speaks for themselves.
I don't know why.
See what all the boys say they're out on the bar.
I know why you, I know why you, but...
Clumsy, for the record, I've never threatened any woman in my life,
whether online or offline.
I want to make a video where you're calling Sandman.
Can you go ahead and try again though?
I mean...
i get the saman part okay try again gaslighter whatever the buddhazi or whatever it's called
why are you calling me a b-tar like i mean do i remember that isn't that the name of that
like that person that called in that day that was b-tardis we got it pretty aggressively
they'll be worse than other people say it it's okay current short oh it's okay
we're trying to be adults right now try again come on
I know what I said, I still have to email jackass don't gas I be
Please please make that more specific when you say that like well diving and like
I
Know I know when I said I got the same emails jackasses. Okay, I've never been any woman online or off like try again
Try again, I have bridge jump many a time. I got the same emails. I'm not hiding anything get the fuck out of here
No, you can't delete emails. I know what I said.
Yeah, there's alligators.
Carl, are you live in Florida?
I am AI right now. I'm AI Carl.
You're starting to look like a Pacific Ocean, you know that?
You're starting to look like a Pacific Ocean.
Oh, I mean, it's very rare.
Look at the chat.
IAX, you're funny, you're funny.
I'm not posting my link.
IAX, you're funny.
OK, OK, OK.
IAX, you're funny, though, you're funny.
Tell me why.
I mean, a lot of this is ridiculous, Carl.
It is, you're right, you're right.
I'll lie to you right now.
Yeah, IAX, IAX too, sometimes I get ridiculous too.
You know what I mean?
Oh
Care for somebody else my link is on the chat
Okay, okay
16 hours a day
What about Tracy? Why do you want to say that about me clumsy? I thought I just sound like being friends
I thought we're a woman that you just
Clumsy
I thought we were cool. That's why I was like, oh, hey, I can invite you to the wedding. I clumsy all my dead parents and my dead brother
I have never asked you to be my best man my my brother my other brother still alive
He was to be my best man
So you gaslit you gaslit fucking clumsy when he said that I asked you be the best man my fuckers
That's my brother my brother would be my get my best man not you homeboy a stranger from the internet get the fuck out of here
Okay, let's address that
You want to guess like me on your fucking panel and you said oh this guy he was weird
I didn't know him. He's asked me to be his best man motherfucker. My brother is my best man
Right. I never asked you to be my best man clumsy. I said I can invite you to the wedding
Yes, just like I did with car hurt beanie. Yes invite. Yes as guests. I never said oh, I
Want to make clumsy my best man
Where where's the proof when you're down the way? Where's where's the proof is it has to be on my on my panel, right?
Or your panel or is in a messaging on Instagram? Where did I say? Hey clumsy? I love you so much
I think you're so cool homeboy. I want you to be my best man. Where did I say that you got to have the clip right?
The clip or the messaging. I never said that stop gaslighting me. Okay, thank you
Tom see you come see you lie a lot. You're sloppy. You're sloppy
How you fucking operate homeboy? Okay? Chill out. Chill out. Okay?
Set all down homeboy set all down and sit down. Okay
Sit down boy. All right the fuck down clumsy little boy
You're weird dude. You're fucking weird for saying that shit. That's fucking weird
I'm not even mad. I'm just fucking correcting your dumbass. Okay
Don't fuck out of here. I asked some fucking stranger from fucking New Mexico to be my best man
Really when my brother's gonna be my fucking best man because I was his best man
Get the fuck out of your own boy or home girl. Should I say cuz we all know you're a fucking hotel
You're a money cone. We all know that now, huh?
When I get married, he's gonna be my best man. That's what I gotta say
That's like you you're gonna be well, congratulations. Congratulations
I got married yet. What the fuck are those people?
When are y'all getting married?
Joe
Well, we really
I haven't met her and we haven't
Isn't that your girlfriend the lady that's with you
No, it's my friend him, but if I did meet a wife, I will get married like I don't know about getting most
Oh, I mean, I'm a girl. I mean, that's just me. I talk about
What am I getting emotional about Tomsy? We really didn't really interact with on Instagram
You know, I said this you said that but we were like really like back and forth, but I don't want you getting that though
Clumsy, I still have my channel. I still have the streams when you join
We had cool interactions. So when did I ever get emotional? You still have your your streams when I joined right?
I'm privatizing. I'll prioritize the ones I have I got nothing to hide. When did I get emotional with you?
Uh, publicly or beyond the scenes comes it come a really we never talked on the phone
So when did I what when did I ever come see again?
You're gaslight when did I ever get emotional when I'm a really man chill out or chill out or really chill out
You know your gaslighting tactics are fucking elementary at best. Okay?
All of it
You're not you're not good at guessing. Okay, just chill out. Just chill out dude. You're not good at guess like chill out
Oh, I'm walking out of horrible
That's scared me
Chill out clumsy chill out. Okay. They are nice bangs. You got a minute. Wow
But I don't hate you man, but I mean I call you up. You know, that's that yeah
What's that? I actually hate you. I actually hate you. Well, you can you don't care if you hate me. That's cool
Now you're what happened you guys you guys
Were you paid attention what I was talking about earlier about clumsy and what he when he the voice point he sent me I
Did and it was creepy. No, no, I'm asking on your next. Oh
The voice that what you played a little while ago, you mean? Yes. Yes. Yes. Oh since then
But what started the bubble?
That's not cool.
I think, again, INX, I mean, I told you,
I had a very good memory from my age.
And you said you did too.
Obviously, you've already forgot, you know?
This is like over and over again.
No, I mean, yeah, I don't know too much of your lore.
I just remember the old were cool.
It's not a lore.
When did it start?
I told, oh my gosh, now you're gaslighting me
because you're acting like.
No, I didn't know what happened.
You were kind of new to me.
I just remember the y'all had a good chat
and I got alive.
Oh my gosh, cool, I'm not.
You have to explain it, I understand, I guess.
Well, how about, I'm gonna do,
I could explain it again right now,
but it's too much, if you can pull back on the stream
right now or later, then you'll hear me explain, yeah.
Okay
All this is just unnecessary it's just I'm good, but then again, too
I'm not complaining because it's the nature of the community. It's a fucked-up toxic
Yes, I mean unlike any other place. So I mean I'm not complaining
I'm not complaining or playing victim because this should happen to me or whatever fuck. No, it's in nature community
I'm not in it
I next but I'm part of it. Yeah, can I kind of say that I'm part of it. So yeah, it's gonna happen. Yeah, it's gonna happen
So whatever. Yeah
It's gonna happen when you do my best man. So if I get married come on man
I need you there. So you're my best man. I don't get married at my best man
I dare I'll call the fucking wedding off. My wife will be like what they gonna bury me
Nigga, that's not me. I need you shown. I swear to God. I fucking see they fucking that yellow. Come on nigga
Oh, that's an evil bastard right there. That's an evil piece of shit
The right now
Who is that in that picture, I don't know who that is I don't know who it is, but I like to lock those lips around
Psyche who is that?
That's Michael Jackson.
That's just Michael Jackson.
Yeah, just Michael Jackson.
Oh, at least she was.
I don't know if she still is.
Okay, Bakelips got a laugh.
Bakelips got his first laugh in my chat, I think.
Aw.
At least she made it last month.
You know what?
Yeah, I mean, I have, I mean, I have like,
I mean, guys, I wish I could like show my archive.
I mean, do you guys see this picture?
Remember your codec, that's the greatest thing, it's like your codec.
I'm going to look up everybody in the codec.
You and Tommy James?
Yeah.
IE Next.
Can I ask you a question?
No, okay. Well, listen, I'm a grown man, right? I can come up anytime like I just stream back then always came up
Right, isn't that funny when salmon comes up? He can never came up never never
So when another man that's came up you will say he came up. What did you say? Oh, what what why you want to see me?
Are you gay? No, I want to see
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Another one of his reputals he will say well, so so saw me on Instagram. Well, that's great
But once you came up right now, you know
On YouTube we're on Instagram came up, but he never will though. I know especially if he's a streamer then came up
I understand some females I can respect that because it's a weird community
You know, I understand that but for a man fucking come up show your face, you know
Oh, fuck you. I'm done, dude. I'm done. I am done. I have nothing to do with that, okay?
You know what? I want to clear one thing up, though. When I said $100,
Psyche, that was to keep Brandon off, because remember he was trying to get down. Yeah. So
that Alex is saying that I
I was offering a hundred dollars. He see a slander's everybody
Records link to this situation can easily be subpoenaed this making it look like we're
Fraud and extortion a clapping it's a clapping for the night
Donation
No, let me see
I even called him for her when he was going at her
You got to go less than 10 I'll be there. Yeah. Yeah. Cool. I put my link in there.
Right now. Okay. I just wanted to come say hi to you, man. And I hope you have a good day. If
you're around, I'll see you around here. I'm looking for my brother over here. He's small,
autistic. Tommy actually did some pretty cool. I got a lot. He did. Yes, he did. He did.
boobies. You can't miss him. If he looks lost, maybe just say, Hey, your brother's looking
for you. Stay here.
Tom salmon, you say that was pretty cool with IRF. He was mine. If I get up to smell you a
little bit closer.
Okay, so he went at salmon and salmon disappeared when Tom see I'm not I'm not begging nothing.
I she talked about going live. So I mean, I told her I'll be there.
Can go live right now, but I don't care about that. It's not doesn't mean that much. What what are they saying?
What they're wanting you were saying. I'm begging I'm begging for you to go live really
It's not about clumsy it's gonna be
No, no, but clumsy just said I'm begging clumsy just every now. I'm begging you to go live right now. Am I begging you? Yeah
No, it's when they're ready. There's it depends on one of those I just told you when you go live
Let's go live, you know be there. Yeah. Okay. Okay. I know
Yeah, it's fucking gas lighter dude. You're a weak gas lighter clumsy chill out chill out on my meds, you know that
That's salmon a gas lighter
Yeah, well thumbs is the same way though. He's the same way you got
He doesn't like it does like salmon, but it's so similar to him back to a piece in a pod. Yeah
Whenever you have a minute, I think I kind of know
Whoo, I'm gonna be honest with you real quick. It smells like my ex-girlfriend over here not in a good way
But that's what we love about seafood, right?
You know, of course, of course, but I just want to make sure that we're going, getting
the best meat for the best price.
I really wish people had- I really wish people had clip my fucking shit back there.
I smell that smell and I'm wondering, is that the product or is that the food?
I can.
I can clip.
I don't know your channel, but now you got- You know what, sir, maybe I see you have
At least it isn't poop tuna. I'm gonna let you go about your work and figure out what I want apparently
I'm not ready
Yes, sir. I'll be back on the way out
He's being too nice. He's being too nice
What you got this is not real aero little taters
Be too nice
ask you to leave we can't have you filming in here oh no filming I was watching a movie yeah I
did see you filming in here yes this is an ip2 oh no no oh okay that's fine I suppose I suppose
I can respect that okay I didn't think yeah so maybe oh maybe that's why he got mad I don't know
yeah that's not ip2 yeah I'll just walk out it's not a big deal
No, he's a pussy. He doesn't want to stream. It's a psychotic episode or anything
I'm not gonna do anything. I'm not gonna do anything weird
Yeah
He's not good after the shit
Someone said that dive was she pulled out the kid they pulled out the Karen phones on the oh
I'm leaving right now. I'm not gonna try to come back in or anything
I didn't do anything wrong.
Then the other one came out.
Because you're going to come back on me.
All right, next. You know how I was arrested?
Are you rostering?
No way. Are you serious?
Recently?
Yep. There was cup holders.
Yep. They were watching me.
I was challenging.
Are you serious?
Yep. And guess what?
And guess what?
Well, I was arrested, but guess what one of my cousins is on the fucking task force. He was a cop
and
I made a job to make a call and he came out and got me off that shit. I got connections. Yeah, yep. I
Didn't want to do I never want to do he was he was off duty down the street and in the cousin's house and I got out that shit
But see I was challenging that I was challenging that day
To a car her beanie was there. He's he's been there from day one
So clumsy you think I'm fucking lying you fucking faggot asked a car beanie
He was there from day one. He's seen my I rough from day one
this was a second or third I wrote string my done and I
Remember I was pressing this one store owner. I was maced by moving down just in time. Oh, yeah
And then after that I went out and I was challenging the cup callers that are watching me
right and
they found out my location and
There was no reason why I was in Walgreens
Troy them in there not like not like this guy fuck no
I had one of the employees slack my phone in my head, you know this guy Tommy Tommy James to fucking soft
he's gonna do I around and
I was going outside and they go we've got the cops and I said I've run this fucking shit
You know everybody step outside and so guess what I stepped outside and fucking RPD Riverside police department over there
I'm like oh fuck but my phone was dying right because I didn't have a battery pack and so guess what I was in the backseat
I was a registered for public intoxication, but there were care. I'm sorry. I annexed there was four cop cars here
I was like why why all these cops for for a public intoxication like
Oh, I was I was trying I was trying the cop cars. They found my location, right?
So I I said make a call he goes home. We're gonna call so I told him my cousin's game, which was the police officer and
Maybe like 10 minutes later. I heard knock on the window and it was my cousin. He said come on cousin
We're going home. He got me out that shit. I was gonna go to jail. He got me out of it
That's that so I went home
He drove me home and his fucking truck right here to lift a truck drove me home, right?
I couldn't drive where I parked and stuff
I couldn't drive you know cuz I was very intoxicated. So he drove me home
He's all you pick up your car the next day. He's like, oh, I heard your life. She must have like yeah
I am I am he's always your time like motherfucker. No mind you. I used to be close to my cousin
He's always hang out get drunk, right?
But I hadn't talked to him in a while and I was like, I'm not gonna do my fucking channel. Yeah, so he took me home
And so I came home charge up my phone and went live again. I say hey fucker. I got out of that shit
You cop callers. I got out of that. I got connections, right?
And yeah, oh we thought you're arrested. Well, I was arrested. I was in the backseat
The copyright told me that I was going down for public intoxication
Going there for eight hours get released, but I don't want to deal with all that fucking. Oh my god eight hours
That's still you gotta you gotta deal with fucking
Gotta go see the judge and gotta get a little fine little slap on the head
I don't deal with any of that shit. So I said make a call and so we made a call to my cousin and
He got me on that shit
that's that now after that I wanted to have my cousin on my stream he's not
gonna show his face but I wouldn't have my cousin on my stream to talk about that
And it sounds like an absurd, but yet if you're there, if you've seen it,
I can't believe myself. I'm just saying. All the people that are watching it, they saw it all.
They saw it. They saw it. They did. Everybody went, how long ago was that? This was three years ago.
Yeah, in 2023. Yeah. So, I mean,
I didn't make this shit up. Everybody saw it live and what women yeah, I bet I bet and so then you ended it after all
I mean
The thing is that I told I told people okay when I should go live my next I
Never had a battery pack right so I should go live when you do IRL rule IRL not these other fucking faggots
It was like last night's like almost three hours or so right when I did a stream and
When the berry died and died I didn't have no berry pack, right? I wasn't I wasn't I wasn't you know streaming like that
And before I went to the Walgreens. I've been very consistent
The whole fucking time my story I said oh shit my battery is like a 5% 7%
I'm going to Walgreens right now. I walked in there smoking a cigarette
So I was told him because Walgreens wants to say that they're all like
Remember they're like remember Walgreens change
INX I know you're here about here. They're trying act like they're trying to be like more health-conscious and shit, right?
They stopped serving alcohol on this stuff. So I mean I want to smoke in a cigarette, you know
Yeah, and that's what got their fucking attention right there. Yeah
Fucking clumsy. He's too much a fucking pussy. He's gonna fucking live stream anything let alone doing that shit
and I was running solo by the way and
Like when I wrapped around that fucking store and that's when the cop cars came through
So when I stepped outside, oh fuck, there was one cop car
I was talking with them. I was arrested and then there was three other cop cars as for total
I'm like, what the fuck for me for in Riverside right now, really?
Public intoxication really all I got cop colors. Yep. Yeah. Yep
Wow, this fucking faggot
That's why I don't
This this fucking snaggle tooth once I talk about doing this and that oh, he's all bad and stuff
I mean do I around boy do I around?
Don't have a set up to carry the camera and all this stuff. I don't know what what am I gonna record?
I just I should tell this guy go I route to go go go to the car shows who do I ride that's cool
That's good content, but mm-hmm. Can we fucking step out of fucking housing do I row he wants to do in his fucking back yard and fucking
What was he doing? He was trying to mock fucking brandy Q. You're just get the fuck out of here
That's a father. Thank you. No, I'm talking about clumsy
Oh
That's as far as this fucking iris going to go you in this fucking backyard right on the side of the house
You're trying to fucking lock
That's as far as your I route homeboy really in your backyard get the fuck out of here
I was out there doing that shit. No clumsy. Go ahead clumsy. Go ahead. Guess I mean guess I mean because guess what your homeboy
Corpina was there from day one. He's seen my all my fucking are all streams
But go ahead guess I mean homeboy say I didn't do any of that shit, right?
I can validate myself. I know what I done
But you're the ones ever there they can validate their own experience
Part being was there from day one. You've seen my shit, right?
Go ahead. Go ahead clumsy cuz you weren't there. You don't see so you want to gaslight fucking coral folk
It's a fuck out of here, dude
Get the fuck out of here. You're fucking shit. It's weak dude clumsy. You're not cut out for gaslight dude chill out dude chill out
Okay, chill out there
Next
Yeah, I'm fucking crazy. I'll tell you there. No, I'm not because it's a character
See when I went out there on your next you put on a character, right?
But there's so many fucking people out here in this fucking city that and that was like what three four years ago
I can go out there the next week and then when you fucking remember me, there's so many fucking people out here, you know
Whatever, but me I didn't go out there all the time acting like that fuck. No, it was a character
Was I trying to get on IP to IP to reach out to me?
IP to soon is reached out to me. I said no
I'm yes
They did yes three of them and IP to reach out to me and again, of course these fuckers that don't know in chat
They're gonna say oh IP dude to reach out to you blah blah blah whatever you weren't there at the time listen
The ones that were there if you know you know and
I did turn down IP2 because I'm not trying to be on that fucking list all those fucking degenerates
Fuck IP2. I was doing my own thing
That's that but I had IP on top of that. I had IP to streamers that wanted to stream with me
But I I never sure with them because I'm not trying to they're trying to leech off of me
I was just doing ira solo. You understand me. Yeah, I'll see yeah
Damn, how long you've been streaming though, you said you did it before well at that time
When I started doing I route that was like for like one or two months and then I
I got to doing the fucking shimmy or the panel shit, but back then we called podcasts, you know
Yeah, but yeah, but me it's not really a flex. I mean imagine me button. I did I wrote this so stupid though
It's not a flex for me. Honestly. It's not I'm not
Fuck this community. I don't give a fuck about this community. I just saying that
What I did how I started, you know
mm-hmm
I started doing like the prison the prison streams and I started to do IRL I did more IRL people that are watching
There was a lot of people they're watching by the way wasn't like no 10 fucking viewers
There was a lot of people if you don't blame me as call her beanie. He was there from day one. He's seen that shit
From day one
He was there from day one and he's seen all that stuff
So I can validate myself, but he can validate his own experience clumsy motherfucker. I'm not gaslighting. Okay
I'm not learning about the either. Okay. I'm not like by any of this shit. Ask a heart beating motherfucker
Ask him
You you
I'm talking to him. I know he's there. I know he's there
I'm not I can't reach out from this this stupid fucking
I can't I can't I can't do it when I'm on the phone. Yeah, I'm not even trying to pull up jeb
I'm saying I know Tom's he was there earlier if he's not that you can play it back. You listen to what I'm saying
So what so car beating was about being gang right being gang, right?
Ask ask
Corrippini
Was car fucker was car full line was he actually do IRL was he doing this shit and Corrippin would say yes
He was he was in this is net. Yes. I was there from day one. Yeah, he did this. He did. Yeah, careful. Yeah
He did he did get arrested. Yeah, he did get out of there. He did all that shit my shit's consistent homeboy
I have nothing like that unlike you
Clumsy you fucking clown clowns II
That should be your fucking name. You're a fucking clown homeboy clowns eat. I'm sorry. I didn't go eat your baby. Yeah, fuck out here
Damn, and eat your baby, but babies
Yeah, that's crazy though
I'm going to go live soon. I mean
I'm wrapping up. Thank you guys so much. It was a great panel. Yeah
You got my channel you can put a comment Carl sod can click on your channel. It's grateful 20
Yeah, oh, yeah. Yeah. Well, I put the link in there. So yeah, my uh
My my channel is retired rookie. That's what it is
rookie
stop okay okay let me see if I find you retired rookie and then now there's a
the retired rookie yeah yeah okay that's okay is that the guy that has bald
hair and a white beard no no please turn it down we can't hear
You don't care. He's ending it. Can you put it in chat before he answers?
That that right there that's that's another guy on on YouTube, I mean, I'm actually
If you can put it in chat before he leaves because he's gonna end it right
Well, I mean
Like I can find I can find your channel. Yeah, I can find my channel and you can
Do I'll comment I'll comment on when you're when you're um, okay, close whatever. Oh, yeah, and then you'll get you'll get my
Okay, cool. That's great. Thank you so much. Okay. Okay. Thanks guys. It was nice meeting you. Okay. Yeah
My next we talked before on beat us panel last year by me. All right, anyways
Yeah, you too you too
Okay, bye. Bye. Love you. Thank you so much. Yeah, and here's I do this for many minutes in one night
No, he's not, he's retired, retired, R-E-T-I-R-D-E-D, rookie.
Okay, I'll be right back.
They spliced my video, they overlaid this
They're so awesome, many words be cate
Ladies and gentlemen, strollers, moderate them
To the greatest criminal, broadcasting wisdom from a folding chair throne
A tarot reader, dream decoder, part-time prophet
Full-time controller, was lax with the IRL cam
A potent chaos from a rusty van
A microphone queen with a coffee addiction
Turning every rumor into primetime fiction
There was Mike with three fake mustaches
Streaming from laundromats, diners and caches
Every trouble he'd deram the mob
He mostly just forgot his stringed ice
We never keep one-ship tarot cards
One-ship stickers, one-sold cursed mob
Internet Snickers
One-delivered noodles, cross-stake, LLDAT
One-accused mch, the criminal mastermind's nap
Tarot Decks, River Duck, X1
Bitch, a burrito named Steve
Who lost his DPS in Reno
Federal agents arrived
Trolls all cheered the
Seven Moth, a novel
Release and Mountain Dukes
The Raman shipment arrived
So peering in the
With the strong old Ash's battle
Dawn said, gather round my children
Put your little fear pants on
She had lore, she had warnings
She had villains in a stack
By the time she hit fraudulent psychic, baby, there was no turning back.
She got a codex and it's sinister obscene, a glittery spreadsheet and a dream.
Girl, he's Google-plone, you say you're above the drama, yet you climbed up on the floor.
You say you're not a character that knows stronger wives by stronger lies,
stronger monologue and he chats a grand design.
Stronger wife on the side, stronger onto this, but you spawn a whole dragon,
fog machine to kill a government name, government name.
She sang it like a prayer, like the social security office
ought to hand her a tiara there.
I'm not a character she cried while posing center stage.
Baby, even Shakespeare whispered,
that's a lot of scene for one page.
She said there's rumors that expect male
secret rings of doom, like every time
Slypes are ravenly.
If someone cash abs lunch, she'll call
guys and quote the book of revelation
with the smoky narrowed.
You say you don't need money. You say you don't need fame. Then why are you giving that every once full name stronger?
Wifi stronger like a scandal in the prosecuting glare. Stronger Wifi stronger cry. Stronger Isle.
Six inch heck is this psychic that jumping through the sky. Girl you stayed just season finale of a war.
You said here was the chatter through the speech it sounded like you wanted dollars joking now that line was looking tacky
But your response was so enormous it came dressed in sequence khaki
You took the little side comment and made it biblical in scope like John Crawford found a live stream and discovered
Christian row cue the cue the choir legal hell fire
I'm unstoppable, soliloquy and fake retire
Cue the, I don't need your friendship
Cue the, I don't need your cash
Then 30 more dramatic, slidly arranged trash
So dumb screamed to now
As though she personally installed the first command prompt on a cow
From bulletin boards to browsers
From dialogue to doom
She walked in like Z-quick obedience
With a gavel and perfume
Meanwhile all the girls in gays and goblins in the chat
We're watching this extravagance of thinking
Well imagine that
A codex made her levitate
A psychic caused a quaking
Somehow every road led back to look at me
For heaven's sake
Stronger wildfire, stronger lies
Stronger's every tale becomes a pageant
When you enter every space
Stronger Wi-Fi, stronger prize
Stronger, I'm the only truth
But your sermon wore a feather bow
And six wigs of you
Codex this and Codex that
Ain't no cake on fire
You turned in each community
Spat into a Greek choir
Stronger Wi-Fi, stronger wise
Stronger need to testify
Out of your show, I'll net
So here's to the song, keep the grand get
Reaction built for all to see she said I'm not a character with her hand posed to the sky
And the entire men unison said, baby, there is a butterfly
It's not about Republicans or Democrats race or gender. It's not about pro this or anti that
It's not about I'm a ginger with the hardy are get it right
I'm gonna stay it and I'm gonna probably regret what I'm gonna say, but I'm gonna stay it
Tommy should have been born
In pre civil war slave times to where I could reasonably call him a nigger
Oh
Yeah
And those times you would be a knicker you're the exact thing. You should have been born black. You're a knicker
I'm with it. I'm with it. Let's go. Come on. Yeah, you are you're a knicker. I'm a ginger. So I'm
About the closest
I
Wouldn't think I ever did for if you had no idea about anything about me
You would be very surprised that I ever been in that world
Diamond you're a hoe shut up. Go say your body
Diamond talk it would you manage flirty diamond?
No, I don't know you with what that person is or does
I don't agree with you.
Would you make money off of them or would you make it with me?
No, I would not because I'm very particular with where my money comes from.
Don't do I don't
What are you talking about?
What's the problem?
I was never taking cream pies.
Never in my life have I took a cream pie
for my fucking money, nasty ass bitch.
You said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you said you
You want to press Zayas so bad bitch? You got the chance to be up in his face to bitch, but not.
What did you do bitch? You ran away like a little bitch. You called him a fucking cop.
Bitch, your blood has fucking HIV. You were so scared of him.
Alex didn't call the cops, you dumbass. Alex didn't call the cops.
He was a bodily motherfucking wolf. Where for on that motherfucker, bitch?
You could have done fucking bodily motherfucking...
Relax, relax. Alex is calling me.
No, what's good, bitch? What's good? You had a lot of shit to say.
And I always want you to handle.
OK, Alex, I got you.
We're going to be here for a little while.
Shout out to the four hour mark.
We're going to continue.
What's that?
Are you going to race quit?
You ready?
No wrong.
We got the content pushing.
You ready?
No wrong.
Are you going to race quit or not?
I'm not going to race quit.
Okay
Three of my towns I need to you block my main account and to my back up. I need to like a scared
Damn you
That's what you is. You a scary hoe.
Why are you just man attacking a woman?
This is a man attacking a woman right now.
Like, what's good?
Because you want to fucking say so much shit.
So what's good?
When are you done or can I talk?
You had all your chances. They said bitch you got no you fucking fucking you
She had enough time if you don't know how to have a conversation with people talking that's not having a convoled
Make me mute Dustin Dustin don't make me mute you go
Go does no all I have to say to you
is that you'll never be a biological woman.
And guys, let's make sure we're fucking in for money,
bitch, we're fucking in for money.
You were wearing a strap on.
You were doing more tranny shit than I did
in my whole fucking life, bitch.
What?
Impossible, that's impossible.
She was using a strap on.
Look at you right there. You're a grown man and you wear the thong and you got fucking you don't know who
And on top of that you're taking cream pies bitch. That's not a transsexual though
I was using a strap on double means he's a transsexual diamond
I'm making a simple fact that she was doing more training shit than I was I never fucked a nigga with a fucking shop on or nothing like that
Like I never fucked a nigga with a fucking shit in that thing
Yeah because you still got dick and balls nigga
Why are you still got a dick?
I never fucked a nigga with a fucking dick
I never fucked a nigga with a shit
He was fucking niggas and let's stop on
Go
I mean, what are you?
One out of time
Tell me if yeah, I don't know who you saying Tommy, but okay. I'm just saying no doctor Tommy
I'm a viking dog. It's a viking saying. Weirdo. Yeah, you're you're a fat drug addict who will never
take you. Enjoy it. By feelings, you might have heard them.
Don't worry
Fucking glaze hug boxes this tonight
This shit makes me sick to my stomach. I thought that I was on fucking panel. So yeah, I got your number
You know
But here's the thing she has me blocked. Yes, we block them my main account
Coward
Giant coward
Why'd you pretend to call the cops on Zaya though
Hey, is that like your pretend trials and your pretend court cases and
Everything like that, right? I thought I was supposed to be in jail
I thought I was supposed to be in trial, remember?
All right, one at a time, go ahead.
I got videos of you fucking simping over me.
Diamond, Diamond, relax.
I didn't know.
One at a time.
I fucking cooked your ass on fucking ETC with pets.
We cooked your ass.
Diamond, shut up.
Dustin, shut up.
Let people talk.
One at a time.
You know, you know, I was going to be on this channel.
You know how it's going to be on the ground.
Wow.
All right.
Shut up.
What nigga?
Calm down, nigga.
Grab your dick and calm down.
Wait.
What is your name?
Dustin?
Dustin.
What's your name?
No, I don't know.
I just called him.
What is it, Todd?
So go ahead, Alex.
Yeah, yeah action a question you see one sense. Yeah, I asked a question. I never got an answer
Let Monica talk
What is there to answer to a fat? Where's my cork?
We're at battle and you don't even know it. It's called the swollen legs wall
You went around telling everyone that I had a court case and you got me served through
a publication and I'm just wondering what the status of that is.
Does it make believe like how you called the cops on Zaya that night, just more make believe
bullshit?
Tommy, you don't matter.
Yeah.
There's no court case.
Is that?
No.
Because there's no court case.
Why are you trying to talk to me?
and there's way too much glazing going on out there.
Every day.
Oh, okay.
And the reality is that you'll never be anything in your life.
Hey, hey, bring back that, uh, what was it, uh,
what was it, the country, country and black girl?
You were on some good shit that night.
You're, you're a country rap,
you're a country rap cyber black girl.
What was that again?
entertain us that you even watch me still shows how public you're a public
figure you're a public figure ma'am goodbye Tommy oh goodbye coward oh we'll
run away with your tail in between your legs come on I know you want to tell me
Fuck no.
It's basically a promise.
Fuck no, you can suck my dick too. Yeah
She was fucking she was a sugar mommy you ain't never had a sugar mama run
I only have one thing to say, and I'm going to say it, and I'm going to probably regret
what I'm going to say, but I'm going to say it, Tommy should have been born in pre-Civil
War slave times to where I could reasonably call him a nigger.
I'm a ginger, I'm a ginger with the hearty are get it right
I'm a ginger with the hearty are I'm your master bitch
I'm your fucking master
Tommy should have been born
I'm your master
I'm leaving wealth all up and down your back bitch
you see how he sounds if you were if you were born in a simple war times that i would be your
master you'd be my bitch no no dallas please absolutely not Tommy you've always been a racist
That's rich. You should have been born black in pre-civil war times. That'd be dope. In those times, you would be a knicker.
No hard on! No hard on!
She's crashing out. Watch it, everybody. She's crashing out.
Oh, damn.
What the hell?
Oh, oh, oh.
No hard on.
Like, when you're in the HIV test, if I could do one, I know for bad, I'm gonna clean.
Oh, they've been begging for her to take one for years.
Oh, I know.
That's like she tried putting it on me.
She said coming out there's someone in their 20s trying
to say that I have AIDS.
Oh, she said I have AIDS, too.
She tried to say that about me, too, so.
That's turned into AIDS, if it's not going to win.
Are you on treatment?
Like, what's going on?
Because you had a lot to say about that regarding me.
And I'm not the one taking cream price
or doing bareback blow jobs.
I don't fuck raw.
I don't suck raw.
I don't even give a hand job raw.
I
You're a prostitute you're a prostitute. Yeah
Talk about a problem
She was successful and she actually rebranded herself.
I'm like,
Khalifa was not so successful.
Yes.
What are you doing?
What are you doing you suckin cheeseburgers David you're a prostitute so I'm by the porn star
Damn, I'll cook you
What kind of bikini is that
What is it you don't make me
Don't shoot ends up
Let's go look at that.
Yeah, that's my phone on Instagram.
Look at that.
What's going on here, son?
That's my ad saying, man.
Yeah, look.
That's all back.
Look at that.
Chill out.
I'm only on here for one reason, you know, you're not gonna get under my skin. I'm on here for one reason only.
Okay, guys, you're getting mad.
Well, I already have said everything I have said, but she's quiet.
I thought her so fucking quiet right now, but listen, back then, I don't mind if my father and you were not expecting this shit right now, because you've been hiding from me.
You don't matter to me.
I
So much that you pretended to call the fucking cop so you're not even a cop calling Karen
Like so what she pretends to make court cases and everything else. I thought I was going to court
Like if I honestly was irrelevant to you you wouldn't have blocked three of my account
Why would I talk to somebody who doesn't matter that's what I was important enough that you made a video about me?
And then I was so important that you ported a video and then I was so important that you blocked three accounts. I
Was that important? Okay, you win. I've never seen Alex this quiet
Yeah, you real happy like you quiet
I've been the whole
What you need you need hit up your old play in anything
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Tommy how's your sister Marie you remember her when you see you're talking to me. Are you talking to me fat nigga?
Yeah, you want it where you want my sister my sister taking bet she take it like you don't like slops like you dog
Yeah
Anymore because Tommy is a child's abuser. Oh really you got proof of that. That's quite a jacket. That's quite a jack
If you like what you see today, consider donating down below, every little bit helps the channel grow. Thank you so much, enjoy.
Yeah, that's what's up girl, that's something sexy.
Look at the table, I make some cookies for you.
Oh, that's fucking awesome, babe.
Do you want me to get a tan?
Nah, you know, you bet it's fun, you know, that's not like camera, because you bet it's fun, and these cookies are good.
I'm glad that this girl's age won't be a problem for you.
Yo, what the fuck?
Go go go ahead and have a seat right there for me, please. I think your name is Brandon
Tell me what you were going to do here today. Oh
I was hanging out with someone just hanging out
Yeah, bro, and how old is the person that you are going to hang out with today, Brandon?
Oh, she's 18.
18?
Yeah.
Well, that's very interesting because I thought that I heard the young ladies say a very different
age, and I believe that she said that she was 15.
Oh, you're so right. I'm getting a little bit older.
My hearing is not what it used to be, but, uh,
but, you know, my vision's still pretty good,
and, uh, I can read the chat logs that you had with the girl
that you were planning on spending time with today.
Yeah, I mean, she told me she was 18 and now.
Oh, really? Really? Is that what the chat logs
are going to read today?
No, I'm not a fucking pedophile, bro.
In a text you had, she said she was 15 years of age and you responded,
oh, I don't give a fuck about all that, you're a sexist fuck.
No, bro, you're taking it out of context.
I'm not a panel.
Oh, you're absolutely right.
And I should add more context and read more
of what you were intending to do with this girl
that you believed was 15 years of age.
I wasn't going to do nothing to her.
I wasn't going to do nothing with her.
Well, you can tell me if I'm making this all up.
Now, I know you're a YouTube streamer from my p-top.
Another one from IP2. I just keep rounding up everybody in that little corner of the internet.
Nah, you're making all this up, bro.
Stop, Brandon! Do not answer one more question, Justin Dan.
Who on earth is that?
You stop right there, white man!
And who am I? Who am I?
I'm the African-American woman that's going to put a stop to your shit right now.
You don't recognize?
You don't recognize who I am?
No.
Well, that figure is considering a million deficient man such as yourself might feel so very inadequate,
perhaps even terrified of an African-American woman of the success and repute such as myself.
Do you realize that I was in a porn parody of the Cosby show?
To stand up for the marginalized and oppressed such as myself,
the people who have been the victim of vicious, hateful, smear campaigns on the internet.
Are you referring to this gentleman here?
This is the man that came to meet a 15-year-old girl.
Oh, many people nowadays are targeted in the Internet for sinister and nefarious reasons.
And it's all for the sake of attention.
And whatever happens, I am there to call it out.
and I am here to call you out today.
Okay, like, let me get this correct.
You're here to protect this gentleman,
this man that came to meet a 15-year-old girl.
Yeah, you're a predator protector.
The last time I checked this for television journalists,
we live in the United States of America.
And here in the United States of America,
we have a legal system.
Whereupon guilt can be attributed
by means of evidence, and by means of a jury.
And until then, all people are innocent until proven guilty.
And if you don't agree with that process, well,
maybe you don't need to be in the United States of America.
Oh, you're absolutely right, whoever you might be.
And in fact, I'm sure that the legal system
would be very interested to know about what this man has
been stating to young girls that he
believed was 15 years of age.
And I'm sure that the legal system
will be very happy to have yet another non-white Latin
American man, Latin American heterosexual man
to destroy, whose life to ruin.
because he is not white, all because he doesn't have the complexion for the protection.
I know that this is all rigged against non-white people. This is extortion.
This is entrapment. Man, this program has caught various different kinds of predators
from different religions, you know, from many people of different positions and ethnicities
And he's enjoying his life as a young man who is Hispanic.
There he is being targeted by some very evil people,
like a certain individual by the name of Ganville.
I have absolutely no idea what that is.
Ganville is an IP2-affiliated streamer who resides in the state of Florida,
who delights in targeting vulnerable individuals.
He's doing this all for attention.
This young man is innocent.
Yeah, he just says shit about me and everybody believes it.
Ganville is an evil, pathetic man that I've never supported in any single way, shape, or form.
I never watched any of his live streams.
I never supported him when N.J. Cortz was giving him attention.
I never imagined or dreamt about licking vanilla ice cream off his chiseled, tattooed chest.
He is absolutely no one and nothing in him is not important.
Gamble is a real fucking predator, bro.
The fuck are you going after him?
Yes, why aren't you going after them, Mr. Hanson?
It's because Gamble has the complexion for the protection.
Well, I don't know what either of you two are talking about.
All I know is that this gentleman right here, he came here to have sex with a 15-year-old
girl.
A girl that he believed was 15 years of age, and who he believed was in this house, but
was actually one of our decoys.
And do you know what you've just caught?
The worst thing you've caught is in a heba file, maybe a heba file.
But not a pedophile believe that it's appropriate for this man to be having
Conversations with a girl who is 15 years of age if I were to have a daughter who was that age and
a man of this man's age would come and try to talk to him
I would rip his head off from where his body stands
with my bare hands.
So aren't you protecting this man here?
Because I believe in standing up for marginalized communities
and these allegations don't make any sense to me.
No, no, that makes any sense.
Well, if you have such a problem with anything that I say.
Why don't you just call 911 and direct them to me?
I'm sure that they'll arrest me.
I don't have to do that.
I just have to wait until this guy steps out from this house
and he gets arrested by the police.
Well, I hope that you have some very strong police officers
to take down this very powerful African-American woman.
Because they'll need to get through me to get to Brandon.
Yeah, there are people that got my back.
You're gonna go to jail now.
Yeah, I know if you liked what you see today leave a like leave a comment down below and of course
Subscribe to stoner scribe. Thank you so much until next time